

let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Abbreviate",
    answer: "The family decided to abbreviate their vacation when a hurricane threatened the island",
    options: [
      "the outside edge of something, if the football across the periphery of the goal line, it is considered a touchdown",
      "优点",
      "The family decided to abbreviate their vacation when a hurricane threatened the island",
      "厌恶人类者 the misanthrope refused to join the community  for their annual holiday party",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "ability",
    answer: "her ability to play piano is staggering, she can play the hardest pieces effortlessly.",
    options: [
      "equal in value, equivalent amounts of money",
      "her ability to play piano is staggering, she can play the hardest pieces effortlessly.",
      "不显眼的the witness saw everything, but the thief wore inconspicuous jeans, so she was not sure how to describe him to the police",
      " sb is financially dependent on sth",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "abridge",
    answer: "The novel was abridged so the students could read it in class",
    options: [
      "the process of emerging, appearance,出现strong emergence, emergence in physics, emergence of the internet",
      "the objective of us is to maintain the world peace",
      "The novel was abridged so the students could read it in class",
      "收回，取回,retrieve or recover something that was lost, she will reclaim the dress she lent to her sister last week",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "abscond",
    answer: "The thief absconded with the jewels",
    options: [
      "to put in a place for safekeeping,堆积，存放 deposit cash in a bank account",
      "to anger, to stimulate, to cause, if you see a snake, do not provoke it or it may strike",
      "The thief absconded with the jewels",
      "his main characteristic was his desire for solitude",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "absorb",
    answer: "we used a sponge to absorb most of the liquid that was spilled",
    options: [
      "to establish the truth, or validity of, there is little evidence to prove you claim that you were in the shower during the crime",
      "粗俗的,he is a crude person",
      "we used a sponge to absorb most of the liquid that was spilled",
      "he adhere to muslim faith",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "abundant",
    answer: "the food at thanksgiving dinner was abundant, we spent the next two weeks to eat leftovers",
    options: [
      "the food at thanksgiving dinner was abundant, we spent the next two weeks to eat leftovers",
      "半透明的",
      "Her persistent cough contradicts her statement that she is feeling well",
      "there is a strong connection between salary and education level",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "accent",
    answer: "强调",
    options: [
      "to give or supply, The tomato plant will yield a huge number of tomatoes",
      "Obey the rules or prepare to suffer the consequences",
      "强调",
      "打败，the thief had to admit defeat when he found the police had surrouned him",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "accept",
    answer: "the athlete was proud to accept the olympic gold medal",
    options: [
      "the bilingual teacher could speak to her student both in english and spanish",
      "His expert of using color and shadow made the painting an aesthetic success",
      "He told his wife everything, she is his confidant",
      "the athlete was proud to accept the olympic gold medal",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "accessible",
    answer: "the presidential palace was accessible only to friends and family",
    options: [
      "精明的he is a shrewd person and he is shrewd enough",
      "优点",
      "the presidential palace was accessible only to friends and family",
      "a fictional place where everything is bad反乌托邦 the hunger games is set in a dydtopia",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "accomplished",
    answer: "stephen king is an accomplished writer, with over forty books to his name",
    options: [
      "not enough, very little, During the great famine in Ireland, food was scarce that many people died of starvation",
      "intense or passionate feelings热情, he roared with the fervor of thousands fans",
      "stephen king is an accomplished writer, with over forty books to his name",
      "放大Tiny cells can be viewed through a microscope because it will magnify them to 400 times their actual size",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "accord",
    answer: "the rival factions ended their war with a peace accord",
    options: [
      "The house features an additional bedroom that could be used as guest room or an office",
      "being the most important force or component统治，主宰,dominant leader/color",
      "the rival factions ended their war with a peace accord",
      "the instructor would never concede that he had made a mistake in grading the exam",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "accumulate",
    answer: "the geologist was hoping to accumulate more rock specimens on his trip out west",
    options: [
      "the geologist was hoping to accumulate more rock specimens on his trip out west",
      "说教的intended to teach or educate, aesop's fables is didactic literature",
      "初步的, it would not likely get past a preliminary hearing, and a judge could potentially criticize the office for doing sth",
      "刺穿的",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "accurate",
    answer: "the data represented by the scientist was accurate",
    options: [
      "the book falls several literary categories, it is both fiction and history",
      "校内的, the intramural football league had teams made up of inhabitants at each of the university's dorms",
      "he is an amateur at golf, he had only hit a ball with the club at once",
      "the data represented by the scientist was accurate",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "acid",
    answer: "the polluted rain was an acid",
    options: [
      "暂时的, he can come back to work when he is feeling better, but in the interim, he should rest",
      "If you compare the living between paris and New York, renting in paris is much cheaper",
      "when I lost my job, my expensive night on the town ceased",
      "the polluted rain was an acid",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "activity",
    answer: "in a large city, there is so much activity that it is difficult to find peace and economy",
    options: [
      "requiring careful attention to detail or skill严苛的he has a very exacting standards",
      "in a large city, there is so much activity that it is difficult to find peace and economy",
      "检察官",
      "啮齿动物",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 16,
    question: "acute",
    answer: "the hound dog has acute sense of smell",
    options: [
      "贬低,sb debased himself by lying to sb",
      "to take care of or look after, I am happy to tend to your plants while you are away on vacation",
      "the objective of us is to maintain the world peace",
      "the hound dog has acute sense of smell",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 17,
    question: "adapt",
    answer: "it will difficult for polar bear to adapt to the changing climate",
    options: [
      "clearly and directly expressed, the instruction is explicit",
      "some people find the concept to immortality difficult to understand",
      "阻碍missing his front teeth impede his ability to speak clearly",
      "it will difficult for polar bear to adapt to the changing climate",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 18,
    question: "abrupt",
    answer: "the passage from winter to spring is very abrupt",
    options: [
      "揭穿to show something is not true, he debunked the company's claim that",
      "the passage from winter to spring is very abrupt",
      "the digital watch the general in the WWII drama wore on his wrist was an anachronism",
      "different, incompatible,不同的 the two cultures were so utterly disparate",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 19,
    question: "aberration",
    answer: "She is normally calm and level headed, so this outburst is an aberration",
    options: [
      "She is normally calm and level headed, so this outburst is an aberration",
      "amicable relations, he is a brilliant, very amicable guy",
      "动量，气势，force or speed of movement, momentum caused the car to coast down the hill",
      "to come before something, smoke and loud noises preceded the volcanic eruption",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 20,
    question: "abhor",
    answer: "Are there any foods that you abhor?",
    options: [
      "警惕的,constantly alert, watchful, wary, the vigilant father guarded at the door to keep the children from seeing the Easter Bunny at work",
      "Are there any foods that you abhor?",
      "to go beyond, she has surpass her original weight lifting goal of 250 pounds",
      "the objective of us is to maintain the world peace",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 21,
    question: "abnegation",
    answer: "To ignore these issues would be a serious abnegation of responsibility",
    options: [
      "Obey the rules or prepare to suffer the consequences",
      "her bright blue shoes contrast sharply with her dark red pants",
      "To ignore these issues would be a serious abnegation of responsibility",
      "C.S. Lewis wrote the history of Narnia in his Chronicles of Narnia series",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 22,
    question: "abstruse",
    answer: "professional philosophers writings often appear abstruse",
    options: [
      "professional philosophers writings often appear abstruse",
      "Ice chips can help alleviate this symptom",
      "something unusual, significant, or impressive, a solar eclipse is a natural phenomenon that some people will never witness",
      "The sound of the car alarm downstairs annoyed the residents who were trying to sleep",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 23,
    question: "adage",
    answer: "谚语He remembered the old adage look before you leap",
    options: [
      "粗俗的,he is a crude person",
      "无法胜任的",
      "The patient heart stopped, the doctor said it was due to cardiac arrest",
      "谚语He remembered the old adage look before you leap",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 24,
    question: "adjure",
    answer: "The judge adjured him to answer truthfully",
    options: [
      "The judge adjured him to answer truthfully",
      "the book falls several literary categories, it is both fiction and history",
      "古董",
      "The look on his face convinced her that he was guilty",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 25,
    question: "adroit",
    answer: "She became adroit at dealing with difficult questions",
    options: [
      "he is a famous architect who designed building so that they would organically fit into their surroundings",
      "it is difficult to concentrate on studying when there is loud music playing",
      "She became adroit at dealing with difficult questions",
      "to live on/in, the family inhabit a small house on a tree-lined street",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 26,
    question: "adulation",
    answer: "He couldn't deal with the adulation of his fans",
    options: [
      "full of doubt, 半信半疑的 Jerry's dubious claim that he could fly like superman",
      "He couldn't deal with the adulation of his fans",
      "If you compare the living between paris and New York, renting in paris is much cheaper",
      "he is an adept basketball player",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 27,
    question: "adulterate",
    answer: "Safforn is very expensive, and is often adulterated with other plants",
    options: [
      "When Alex asked her mom if they could go to the museum, she responded, certainly",
      "complete distance around the shape,周长, the security guard patrolled the perimeter of the property to ensure...",
      "假说 the science experiment proved the student's hypothesis was false",
      "Safforn is very expensive, and is often adulterated with other plants",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 28,
    question: "adumbrate",
    answer: "with assistance from the victim, the sketch artist will adumbrate a picture of the robbery suspect",
    options: [
      "with assistance from the victim, the sketch artist will adumbrate a picture of the robbery suspect",
      "不复存在 sth is defunct",
      "change or exchange, the governor's shift in opinions was unexpected",
      "Charilie was worried that he had a cancer, but the lump on his leg turned out to be benign",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 29,
    question: "adversity",
    answer: "How do you deal with adversity in life/work?",
    options: [
      "The children chanted as they sang ring around the rosie",
      "评论家，critics said the movie was horrible",
      "Ice chips can help alleviate this symptom",
      "How do you deal with adversity in life/work?",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 30,
    question: "Adaptation",
    answer: "The cactus has developed an adaptation that allows it survive without water for months at a time",
    options: [
      "The cactus has developed an adaptation that allows it survive without water for months at a time",
      "to serve as a warning or prediction伏笔,the dark clouds foreshadow a great storm apporaching",
      "The thief absconded with the jewels",
      "Safforn is very expensive, and is often adulterated with other plants",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 31,
    question: "additional",
    answer: "The house features an additional bedroom that could be used as guest room or an office",
    options: [
      "to depict visually or describe in words, she portrayed her boyfriend as tall, even though he was in fact short",
      "Amy begrudged Jo's book so much that she destroyed it in a fit of jealousy",
      "The house features an additional bedroom that could be used as guest room or an office",
      "Since Rhonda only answered three of the ten questions, she was certain she had failed the exam",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 32,
    question: "address",
    answer: "The president's speech was an address to congress",
    options: [
      "The patient heart stopped, the doctor said it was due to cardiac arrest",
      "climatic changes have been reported in the sourthern regions, many of which have been experiencing record high temperatures",
      "The president's speech was an address to congress",
      "To say that something has an amorphous shape, is a contradiction. How can a shape be shapeless",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 33,
    question: "adept",
    answer: "he is an adept basketball player",
    options: [
      "he is an adept basketball player",
      "胜诉, achieving success in legal proceeding, the likelihood of prevailing in court was pretty low.",
      "证书display the credential in a frame on the wall",
      "可信的，the story was not credible",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 34,
    question: "adequate",
    answer: "She makes an adequate amount of money, but she still could not afford to go on a fancy vacation",
    options: [
      "华丽的beautiful, elaborate, or extravagant, the singers gave a magnificent performance",
      "The country faced complex economic problems that stemmed from a variety of different causes.",
      "She makes an adequate amount of money, but she still could not afford to go on a fancy vacation",
      "an introductory chapter or event, 序幕，开场白, the prologue to the play set the scene for what I was about to see",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 35,
    question: "adhere",
    answer: "The student put the glue on the back of the paper, so that it would adhere to the poster",
    options: [
      "The conference featured a broad range of topics, including everything from astrology to exercise",
      "The student put the glue on the back of the paper, so that it would adhere to the poster",
      "Some people do not like eating foods with mushy consistency",
      "挥霍",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 36,
    question: "adhere_2",
    answer: "he adhere to muslim faith",
    options: [
      "The wealthy benefactor wished to remain anonymous; she didn't want anyone to know her name",
      "he adhere to muslim faith",
      "玷污,hate to defile it by doing sth",
      "笨拙的",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 37,
    question: "adjacent",
    answer: "Our house is adjacent to the corner store",
    options: [
      "不复存在 sth is defunct",
      "to join the photograph club, you must posses a high-quality, black and write camera",
      "Our house is adjacent to the corner store",
      "The historian referred to the annals of 10th century Egyptians to write his paper",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 38,
    question: "advanced",
    answer: "only the most advanced students can truly understand the fermi paradox",
    options: [
      "投掷，愤慨的说，Blackburn said last week that the man in the Coolla was waiting for his spot, and hurled insults in his direction",
      "恶意的，恶毒的the debate turned negative when one candidate maliciously attacked the character of his opponent",
      "狡猾的she had a sly personality/sly sip of water",
      "only the most advanced students can truly understand the fermi paradox",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 39,
    question: "advantages",
    answer: "one of the many advantages of living in the country is that the air is cleaner",
    options: [
      "one of the many advantages of living in the country is that the air is cleaner",
      "无法胜任的",
      "诡计多端的",
      "to depict visually or describe in words, she portrayed her boyfriend as tall, even though he was in fact short",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 40,
    question: "advocate",
    answer: "she was a tireless advocate for peace",
    options: [
      "Because it is not allowed in school, student kept a secret stach of contraband candy in her locker",
      "she was a tireless advocate for peace",
      "not complete, we have only partial understanding of our universal",
      "The boss will chastise the employees for leaving early",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 41,
    question: "aesthetic",
    answer: "His expert of using color and shadow made the painting an aesthetic success",
    options: [
      "coming into being,新出现的, an emerging market, cade slowly emerging from his shell",
      "警惕的,constantly alert, watchful, wary, the vigilant father guarded at the door to keep the children from seeing the Easter Bunny at work",
      "the heavy rain was an antecedent event to the flooding that occurred",
      "His expert of using color and shadow made the painting an aesthetic success",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 42,
    question: "affect",
    answer: "I hope your illness does not affect your ability to work.",
    options: [
      "警惕的,constantly alert, watchful, wary, the vigilant father guarded at the door to keep the children from seeing the Easter Bunny at work",
      "The judge adjured him to answer truthfully",
      "I hope your illness does not affect your ability to work.",
      "a social blunder, an embarrassing mistake, 失礼, burping after you eat it's considered a gaffe",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 43,
    question: "agree",
    answer: "I hope we can agree on a good time for us to meet.",
    options: [
      "I hope we can agree on a good time for us to meet.",
      "Are there any foods that you abhor?",
      "碎片, dropped vase shattered into a dozen fragments",
      "I was concerned when you didn't show up for work at the usual time",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 44,
    question: "altercation",
    answer: "After the car accident, the drivers got upset and had an altercation",
    options: [
      "After the car accident, the drivers got upset and had an altercation",
      "啮齿动物",
      "The cactus has developed an adaptation that allows it survive without water for months at a time",
      "to discourage阻止，震慑a dog will deter thieves from ...",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 45,
    question: "alternative",
    answer: "we want an outdoor wedding, but we have an alternative locations if it rains",
    options: [
      "associated with the country life, I love big citys, but sometimes I crave the peace and solitude of rural life",
      "不朽，不死,the vampire is mythical creature that is usually described as immortal",
      "Her apartment consists of three rooms: a bedroom, a bathroom, and a kitchen",
      "we want an outdoor wedding, but we have an alternative locations if it rains",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 46,
    question: "altruistic",
    answer: "The minister was an altruistic man who gave the money he earned to the community",
    options: [
      "Some people do not like eating foods with mushy consistency",
      "The minister was an altruistic man who gave the money he earned to the community",
      "the rival factions ended their war with a peace accord",
      "The paster has authority to marry the couple",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 47,
    question: "amateur",
    answer: "he is an amateur at golf, he had only hit a ball with the club at once",
    options: [
      "The man was ambivalent about where to eat dinner, he couldn't decide between fish and chickens",
      "I awoke in the middle night to a loud clamor, my neighbors were arguing again",
      "he is an amateur at golf, he had only hit a ball with the club at once",
      "假说 the science experiment proved the student's hypothesis was false",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 48,
    question: "ambient",
    answer: "The elevator music provided ambient noise while passengers rode to their floors ",
    options: [
      "The elevator music provided ambient noise while passengers rode to their floors ",
      "All this appears in the form of a story or fabel, called an allegory",
      "The most exciting part of the film's permiere was when the lead actress made his appearance",
      "优点",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 49,
    question: "ambiguous",
    answer: "Sara gave an ambiguous answer to the lawyer's question",
    options: [
      "different, incompatible,不同的 the two cultures were so utterly disparate",
      "My contribution to the bake sale was three dozen oatmeal-raised cookies",
      "He amalgamate his company with another",
      "Sara gave an ambiguous answer to the lawyer's question",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 50,
    question: "ambitious",
    answer: "the students were ambitious, they wanted to learn everything the school could teach them",
    options: [
      "the students were ambitious, they wanted to learn everything the school could teach them",
      "饥荒",
      "The boy who broke the lamp wasn't the boy who was punished, it was frustratingly arbitrary",
      "the data represented by the scientist was accurate",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 51,
    question: "ambivalent",
    answer: "The man was ambivalent about where to eat dinner, he couldn't decide between fish and chickens",
    options: [
      "aggregate number of unemployed",
      "The professor applied chemistry theory to the equation and come up with the correct answer",
      "To ignore these issues would be a serious abnegation of responsibility",
      "The man was ambivalent about where to eat dinner, he couldn't decide between fish and chickens",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 52,
    question: "amiable",
    answer: "the golden retreiver was amiable, she excitedly greeted every person he saw",
    options: [
      "湿透的，she liked how inexpensive she's umbrella was, up untill it's poor quality left her drenched in the rain",
      "the golden retreiver was amiable, she excitedly greeted every person he saw",
      "千年The epic science-fiction novel told the story of an alien society over the course of a millennium",
      "假说 the science experiment proved the student's hypothesis was false",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 53,
    question: "amorous",
    answer: "On Valentine's day, Farhad was feeling amorous, so he took his girlfriend to a romantic dinner",
    options: [
      "fulfilling all requirements, the maid's cleanup was satisfactory, but not outstanding",
      "On Valentine's day, Farhad was feeling amorous, so he took his girlfriend to a romantic dinner",
      "见多识广，四海为家的人, a truly cosmopolitan traveler",
      "we used a sponge to absorb most of the liquid that was spilled",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 54,
    question: "amphitheater",
    answer: "While on vacation, the students visited an amphitheater in Rome called the Colosseum",
    options: [
      "While on vacation, the students visited an amphitheater in Rome called the Colosseum",
      "the two ends of range, death valley has great extremes of heat and cold",
      "The paster has authority to marry the couple",
      "梅雨",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 55,
    question: "analysis",
    answer: "our analysis of the project revealed that it was made of carbon",
    options: [
      "夸张",
      "折断，the tension on the rope was so tight that he was afraid it would snap at any time",
      "in a large city, there is so much activity that it is difficult to find peace and economy",
      "our analysis of the project revealed that it was made of carbon",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 56,
    question: "analyze",
    answer: "we must analyze your test to determine what you need to improve",
    options: [
      "Given that you hate crowds, I assumed you wouldn't want my extra tickets for the concert tonight",
      "仪式，one of the group's religious ritual is to abstain from eating break for a week.",
      "we must analyze your test to determine what you need to improve",
      "he is a famous architect who designed building so that they would organically fit into their surroundings",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 57,
    question: "anachronism ",
    answer: "the digital watch the general in the WWII drama wore on his wrist was an anachronism",
    options: [
      "刺穿的",
      "they are differ in many areas: hair colors..",
      "镜头,Danville Costco video Footage shows both men could have walked away, DA",
      "the digital watch the general in the WWII drama wore on his wrist was an anachronism",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 58,
    question: "annals",
    answer: "The historian referred to the annals of 10th century Egyptians to write his paper",
    options: [
      "含义，意味, when you said I looked healthy, was that really an implication that I have put on weight?",
      "The two countries held a bilateral meeting in a neutral location",
      "to go beyond, she has surpass her original weight lifting goal of 250 pounds",
      "The historian referred to the annals of 10th century Egyptians to write his paper",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 59,
    question: "anomaly",
    answer: "The aurora borealis is usually seen in high latitude regions like the arctic, so it would be an anomaly if it were seen in New england",
    options: [
      "to come into view, often from a hidden place,出来，产生，plane emerge from the clouds",
      "The aurora borealis is usually seen in high latitude regions like the arctic, so it would be an anomaly if it were seen in New england",
      "The country faced complex economic problems that stemmed from a variety of different causes.",
      "假说 the science experiment proved the student's hypothesis was false",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 60,
    question: "annoyed",
    answer: "The sound of the car alarm downstairs annoyed the residents who were trying to sleep",
    options: [
      "providing an immediate advantage,应急之际 it is expedient to do something",
      "The sound of the car alarm downstairs annoyed the residents who were trying to sleep",
      "change or exchange, the governor's shift in opinions was unexpected",
      "the hound dog has acute sense of smell",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 61,
    question: "annual",
    answer: "the parade is an annual affair",
    options: [
      "an earlier occurrence of something similar, the school set a precedent that all students could dye their hair unusual color by allowing ont student to do so ",
      "刺穿的",
      "群居Dophins are a gregarious species of oceanic mammal",
      "the parade is an annual affair",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 62,
    question: "anonymous",
    answer: "The wealthy benefactor wished to remain anonymous; she didn't want anyone to know her name",
    options: [
      "having free will，自主性, he made a voluntary decision to confess, hoping that his cooperation would reduce his punishment",
      "the outside edge of something, if the football across the periphery of the goal line, it is considered a touchdown",
      "The wealthy benefactor wished to remain anonymous; she didn't want anyone to know her name",
      "fresh, original新颖的, Ray had a novel approach to homework, he did the work before it was assigned",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 63,
    question: "antecedent ",
    answer: "the heavy rain was an antecedent event to the flooding that occurred",
    options: [
      "刺激to excite or rouse to action, Caffine can often stimulate us to get out of bed",
      "I awoke in the middle night to a loud clamor, my neighbors were arguing again",
      "the heavy rain was an antecedent event to the flooding that occurred",
      "石板的教师，the pedagogue in charge of my history class refused to let us change seats, because",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 64,
    question: "anthropology",
    answer: "Those who had studied anthropology were excited to see the earliest known cookbook at the museum",
    options: [
      "信任",
      "Those who had studied anthropology were excited to see the earliest known cookbook at the museum",
      "稠密 a dense cluster of stars, a dense population",
      "her ability to play piano is staggering, she can play the hardest pieces effortlessly.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 65,
    question: "anticipate ",
    answer: "the dark clouds made him anticipate a storm",
    options: [
      "the dark clouds made him anticipate a storm",
      "he is an adept basketball player",
      "碎片, dropped vase shattered into a dozen fragments",
      "well-being, happiness or health, 福利，the country provided free health coverage for the welfare of its citizens",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 66,
    question: "antidote ",
    answer: "when the gardener was bit by the snake, the doctor give him an antidote to prevent the posion from taking effect",
    options: [
      "机能失调的 the dysfunctional family fought so loudly",
      "when the gardener was bit by the snake, the doctor give him an antidote to prevent the posion from taking effect",
      "not enough, very little, During the great famine in Ireland, food was scarce that many people died of starvation",
      "The couple's daily commute was an important consideration in buying a house",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 67,
    question: "appeal ",
    answer: "Eating snails is something that does not appeal to me",
    options: [
      "we must analyze your test to determine what you need to improve",
      "唤醒",
      "分散 police dispersed the crowd.",
      "Eating snails is something that does not appeal to me",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 68,
    question: "appealing",
    answer: "with their soft fur and large eyes, puppies are appealing to almost everyone",
    options: [
      "After Tara learned that her finace had lied to her, she decided to cancel the wedding",
      "with their soft fur and large eyes, puppies are appealing to almost everyone",
      "short trip短途旅行take a one-day excursion to sp nearby",
      "谚语He remembered the old adage look before you leap",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 69,
    question: "appearance",
    answer: "The most exciting part of the film's permiere was when the lead actress made his appearance",
    options: [
      "The most exciting part of the film's permiere was when the lead actress made his appearance",
      "徘徊,we lingered at the beach well after sunset",
      "Most kids feels pressure to conform to the standards of their peers",
      "Eating snails is something that does not appeal to me",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 70,
    question: "appease",
    answer: "Congress was forced to compromise in order to appease the holdouts",
    options: [
      "The united way, like any charity, is an benevolent organization",
      "Congress was forced to compromise in order to appease the holdouts",
      "the cause of my lateness was that the bus broke down and I had to work 10 blocks.",
      "改革，how about fighting against gun reform laws that could prevent school shootings",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 71,
    question: "applied",
    answer: "The professor applied chemistry theory to the equation and come up with the correct answer",
    options: [
      "不复存在 sth is defunct",
      "说客",
      "an aggregate flower; an aggregate fruit(strawberry, raspberry, blackberry)",
      "The professor applied chemistry theory to the equation and come up with the correct answer",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 72,
    question: "appreciate",
    answer: "we often do not appreciate the best things in life until they have been taken away from us.",
    options: [
      "we often do not appreciate the best things in life until they have been taken away from us.",
      "existing perpetually without change",
      "The groundhog was very circumspect as he slowly came out of his hole",
      "the students were ambitious, they wanted to learn everything the school could teach them",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 73,
    question: "approach",
    answer: "The celebrity was so intimidating, I was not sure how to approach him",
    options: [
      "石板的教师，the pedagogue in charge of my history class refused to let us change seats, because",
      "climatic changes have been reported in the sourthern regions, many of which have been experiencing record high temperatures",
      "The celebrity was so intimidating, I was not sure how to approach him",
      "common or widespread, cell phones are so prevalent in Italy, that many people no longer use land lines",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 74,
    question: "appropriate",
    answer: "The business suit is appropriate attire for the job interview",
    options: [
      "His affectation was just a facade he put up to hide his true self.",
      "she was a tireless advocate for peace",
      "a stupid or foolish person, you are shithead bozo",
      "The business suit is appropriate attire for the job interview",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 75,
    question: "approximately",
    answer: "my plane will arrive at approximately 9 pm",
    options: [
      "破坏，the children's adamant refusal to learn french considerably undermines their teacher's effort",
      "贬低,sb debased himself by lying to sb",
      "Safforn is very expensive, and is often adulterated with other plants",
      "my plane will arrive at approximately 9 pm",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 76,
    question: "arbitrary",
    answer: "The boy who broke the lamp wasn't the boy who was punished, it was frustratingly arbitrary",
    options: [
      "I hope your illness does not affect your ability to work.",
      "A beneficiary is a person who is designed to receive the benefit of the property owned by someone else",
      "common or widespread, cell phones are so prevalent in Italy, that many people no longer use land lines",
      "The boy who broke the lamp wasn't the boy who was punished, it was frustratingly arbitrary",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 77,
    question: "archetype",
    answer: "Romeo and Juliet is a perfect archetype of the genre",
    options: [
      "暂时的, he can come back to work when he is feeling better, but in the interim, he should rest",
      "The children chanted as they sang ring around the rosie",
      "prep regardless of; without being affected by, Despite her many challenges,...",
      "Romeo and Juliet is a perfect archetype of the genre",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 78,
    question: "architect",
    answer: "he is a famous architect who designed building so that they would organically fit into their surroundings",
    options: [
      "he is a famous architect who designed building so that they would organically fit into their surroundings",
      "an introductory chapter or event, 序幕，开场白, the prologue to the play set the scene for what I was about to see",
      "her ability to play piano is staggering, she can play the hardest pieces effortlessly.",
      "to go beyond, she has surpass her original weight lifting goal of 250 pounds",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 79,
    question: "argue",
    answer: "Let's try not to argue over who wash dishes tonight",
    options: [
      "going beyond what is on the surface, deep,深刻的，深入的，she gave us a profound understanding of human life",
      "she was a tireless advocate for peace",
      "夸张",
      "Let's try not to argue over who wash dishes tonight",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 80,
    question: "artificial",
    answer: "the hokey player had several artificial teeth to replace the ones he had lost during the season",
    options: [
      "existing below the threshold of consciousness潜意识的,since buliminal suggestions exists beneath our concious levels of thought",
      "the hokey player had several artificial teeth to replace the ones he had lost during the season",
      "夸张",
      "转移，the police diverted traffic to a side street",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 81,
    question: "artistic",
    answer: "she was so artistic that even her fruit bowel arranged in a beautiful manner",
    options: [
      "she was so artistic that even her fruit bowel arranged in a beautiful manner",
      "Safforn is very expensive, and is often adulterated with other plants",
      "willing to obey someone else, the youngest wolves submissive to the older, stronger more experienced wolves",
      "辩护人",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 82,
    question: "assess",
    answer: "you must assess the effort you have put in to the task",
    options: [
      "felt ambivalence toward his powerful father, ambivalence toward marriage",
      "The children chanted as they sang ring around the rosie",
      "the country's involvement in its neighbors affairs has caused quite a controversy",
      "you must assess the effort you have put in to the task",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 83,
    question: "assignment",
    answer: "I was very busy this week, so I was unable to complete the homework assignment",
    options: [
      "when jahnavi forgot her mom's birthday, she sent a belated birthday gift a week later.",
      "the passage from winter to spring is very abrupt",
      "I was very busy this week, so I was unable to complete the homework assignment",
      "挥霍",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 84,
    question: "assistance",
    answer: "The old woman required assistance when getting in and out of cars",
    options: [
      "The old woman required assistance when getting in and out of cars",
      "it is important to understand how the historians reached this conclusion",
      "折断，the tension on the rope was so tight that he was afraid it would snap at any time",
      "暂时的, he can come back to work when he is feeling better, but in the interim, he should rest",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 85,
    question: "assumed",
    answer: "Given that you hate crowds, I assumed you wouldn't want my extra tickets for the concert tonight",
    options: [
      "Given that you hate crowds, I assumed you wouldn't want my extra tickets for the concert tonight",
      "The minister was an altruistic man who gave the money he earned to the community",
      "before buying a dog, you need to consider whether or not you'll be able to take care of it",
      "the objective of us is to maintain the world peace",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 86,
    question: "assumptions",
    answer: "I made some assumptions about Dana's character without really knowing her",
    options: [
      "an introductory chapter or event, 序幕，开场白, the prologue to the play set the scene for what I was about to see",
      "to redicule, to laugh at, 嘲弄 sb deride sb's driving ability",
      "I made some assumptions about Dana's character without really knowing her",
      "刺激to excite or rouse to action, Caffine can often stimulate us to get out of bed",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 87,
    question: "attention",
    answer: "Make sure to make attention in class, or you will have trouble with the homework",
    options: [
      "After the car accident, the drivers got upset and had an altercation",
      "Make sure to make attention in class, or you will have trouble with the homework",
      "煽动，鼓动，plainly be constructed as incitement to violence",
      "concerned with ordinary activities or business, I loved pink hat, but my more practical side won out, and I decided not to buy it",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 88,
    question: "attitude",
    answer: "she has such an enthusiastic attitude the everyone enjoyed being around her",
    options: [
      "she has such an enthusiastic attitude the everyone enjoyed being around her",
      "精明的he is a shrewd person and he is shrewd enough",
      "不显眼的the witness saw everything, but the thief wore inconspicuous jeans, so she was not sure how to describe him to the police",
      "the polluted rain was an acid",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 89,
    question: "attributed",
    answer: "Molly attributed her frustration to her lack of sleep",
    options: [
      "hard to pin down, evasive, 难以琢磨的，困难的the answer to this question was elusive",
      "The most exciting part of the film's permiere was when the lead actress made his appearance",
      "to maintain or keep alive, in order to preserve fresh bread, make sure to keep it in dark, air-tight place",
      "Molly attributed her frustration to her lack of sleep",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 90,
    question: "auctioned",
    answer: "When the recluse died, his vast art collection was auctioned to raise money for community",
    options: [
      "The angry school board circumvented the students's efforts to install televesions in ever classroom",
      "夸张，example of hyperbole, I am so hungry, I could eat a house",
      "When the recluse died, his vast art collection was auctioned to raise money for community",
      "to compete, Sheryl vied with her best friend for a promotion",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 91,
    question: "augment ",
    answer: "The photographer wanted to augment her income by shooting weddings on the weekends",
    options: [
      "fresh, original新颖的, Ray had a novel approach to homework, he did the work before it was assigned",
      "放大Tiny cells can be viewed through a microscope because it will magnify them to 400 times their actual size",
      "The photographer wanted to augment her income by shooting weddings on the weekends",
      "The historian referred to the annals of 10th century Egyptians to write his paper",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 92,
    question: "affectation",
    answer: "His affectation was just a facade he put up to hide his true self.",
    options: [
      "coming into being,新出现的, an emerging market, cade slowly emerging from his shell",
      "犯规，污秽",
      "Her persistent cough contradicts her statement that she is feeling well",
      "His affectation was just a facade he put up to hide his true self.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 93,
    question: "aggregate",
    answer: "an aggregate flower; an aggregate fruit(strawberry, raspberry, blackberry)",
    options: [
      "an aggregate flower; an aggregate fruit(strawberry, raspberry, blackberry)",
      "to escape, to avoid逃避，规避，回避 celebrity evade paparazzi on XXX",
      "栖息地snakes perfer a sunny and dry habitat",
      "a fictional place that where everything is good乌托邦",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 94,
    question: "aggregate_2",
    answer: "aggregate number of unemployed",
    options: [
      "aggregate number of unemployed",
      "we often do not appreciate the best things in life until they have been taken away from us.",
      "aggregate number of unemployed",
      "粗俗的,he is a crude person",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 95,
    question: "akrasia",
    answer: "What is Akrasia and how to overcome it",
    options: [
      "skillful, adroit机敏的，灵巧的sb is dexterous negotiator/debater/hands",
      "分发，分配，sb distribute sth to someplace",
      "the athlete was proud to accept the olympic gold medal",
      "What is Akrasia and how to overcome it",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 96,
    question: "alacrity",
    answer: "She roses with alacrity and moved away",
    options: [
      "the act of mentioning something, At lunch, he made a reference to the fact he...",
      "a stupid or foolish person, you are shithead bozo",
      "we want an outdoor wedding, but we have an alternative locations if it rains",
      "She roses with alacrity and moved away",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 97,
    question: "allegory",
    answer: "All this appears in the form of a story or fabel, called an allegory",
    options: [
      "睫毛膏",
      "to reduce or take away the value of有损于 sth will not detract sb's joy/fame",
      "All this appears in the form of a story or fabel, called an allegory",
      "The children chanted as they sang ring around the rosie",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 98,
    question: "alleviate",
    answer: "Ice chips can help alleviate this symptom",
    options: [
      "well-spoken,有说服力的 The speaker was so eloquent",
      "the distance around the campus is about 3 miles, so I had to complete the circuit twice to run 6 miles.",
      "The new information only confused the situation",
      "Ice chips can help alleviate this symptom",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 99,
    question: "illusion",
    answer: "The beginning of the books has an illusion which hints at how the book ends",
    options: [
      "起诉，there was not enough evidence to bring prosecution on this case",
      "Jes couldn't play sports due to her chronic asthma",
      "The professor applied chemistry theory to the equation and come up with the correct answer",
      "The beginning of the books has an illusion which hints at how the book ends",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 100,
    question: "amalgamate",
    answer: "He amalgamate his company with another",
    options: [
      "to offer or hold out to someone for acceptance, 提供，提出，because your proffer of repayment for the movie tickets was too little, I will not buy them to you",
      "He amalgamate his company with another",
      "to use up花费expend financial resources on sth",
      "the state or condition of being equal, it is impossible to establish parity in grades, because...",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 101,
    question: "ambivalence",
    answer: "felt ambivalence toward his powerful father, ambivalence toward marriage",
    options: [
      "with assistance from the victim, the sketch artist will adumbrate a picture of the robbery suspect",
      "felt ambivalence toward his powerful father, ambivalence toward marriage",
      "至关重要,the children didn't think clean up playroom is imperative",
      "to regard with contempt蔑视, sb didained sb for sth",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 102,
    question: "ambivalence_2",
    answer: "ambivalence about their goals, why our ambivalence?",
    options: [
      "When the recluse died, his vast art collection was auctioned to raise money for community",
      "Her background in Roman Language was helpful in her trip to Europe",
      "ambivalence about their goals, why our ambivalence?",
      "my plane will arrive at approximately 9 pm",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 103,
    question: "amend",
    answer: "amended the manuscript, amend the situation, amend a constitution",
    options: [
      "in a large city, there is so much activity that it is difficult to find peace and economy",
      "amended the manuscript, amend the situation, amend a constitution",
      "糖尿病患者",
      "发明",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 104,
    question: "amicable",
    answer: "amicable relations, he is a brilliant, very amicable guy",
    options: [
      "amicable relations, he is a brilliant, very amicable guy",
      "车门锁,快速走进，The driver of a dark car latches onto a white car",
      "he is a famous architect who designed building so that they would organically fit into their surroundings",
      "故障，失灵The robotic vaccum cleaner worked for monthes before it started to malfunction",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 105,
    question: "anachronistic",
    answer: "the use of rotary phone in the modern world is considered anachronistic",
    options: [
      "tending to bring together or unite, attending sports events can have a unifying effect on a community",
      "very small, The baby spider was so minute that one could barely see them",
      "the use of rotary phone in the modern world is considered anachronistic",
      "the dark clouds made him anticipate a storm",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 106,
    question: "authority",
    answer: "The paster has authority to marry the couple",
    options: [
      "The paster has authority to marry the couple",
      "clearly and directly expressed, the instruction is explicit",
      "a social blunder, an embarrassing mistake, 失礼, burping after you eat it's considered a gaffe",
      " My guidance counselor belittled my high school record by telling me that not everybody belongs in colledge.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 107,
    question: "automatic",
    answer: "The automatic dishwasher cleans the dishes without any work from the chef",
    options: [
      "宿舍",
      "The minister was an altruistic man who gave the money he earned to the community",
      "The man was ambivalent about where to eat dinner, he couldn't decide between fish and chickens",
      "The automatic dishwasher cleans the dishes without any work from the chef",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 108,
    question: "autonomous",
    answer: "After years being under Soviet rule, Lithuania finally became an autonomous nation in 1900 ",
    options: [
      "After years being under Soviet rule, Lithuania finally became an autonomous nation in 1900 ",
      "州际公路the family drove through an interstate highway from their home in Texas to their new home Florida",
      "The old woman required assistance when getting in and out of cars",
      "to appease or soothe, the beleaguered general tried to pacify his fierce attacker by sending him a flower",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 109,
    question: "autonomy",
    answer: "freedom from external control, The Mohegan tribe has full autonomy on its own reservation",
    options: [
      "徘徊,we lingered at the beach well after sunset",
      "the instructor would never concede that he had made a mistake in grading the exam",
      "短暂的flowers are ephemeral",
      "freedom from external control, The Mohegan tribe has full autonomy on its own reservation",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 110,
    question: "Availability",
    answer: "The popular hotel is in such demand, that it  has limited availability.",
    options: [
      "The popular hotel is in such demand, that it  has limited availability.",
      "he adhere to muslim faith",
      "the polluted rain was an acid",
      "Since Rhonda only answered three of the ten questions, she was certain she had failed the exam",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 111,
    question: "Available",
    answer: "The shoes I wanted to order from the store are, unfortunately, no longer available",
    options: [
      "traits or qualities of something, one of the properties of dry ice is that it is very cold",
      "判决书",
      "something unusual, significant, or impressive, a solar eclipse is a natural phenomenon that some people will never witness",
      "The shoes I wanted to order from the store are, unfortunately, no longer available",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 112,
    question: "Aware",
    answer: "Soldiers need to be aware of potential danger at all times, even when they least expect it.",
    options: [
      "to spread throughout, the small of my mom's cookies is starting to pervade my room and make my mouth water",
      "ZIN uh foh bee uh, a fear of people from other countries, Despite his xenophobia, he packed his bags, got on the plane, and started to explore different countries",
      "Soldiers need to be aware of potential danger at all times, even when they least expect it.",
      "围困",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 113,
    question: "background",
    answer: "Her background in Roman Language was helpful in her trip to Europe",
    options: [
      "Her background in Roman Language was helpful in her trip to Europe",
      "使遭受，使承受the lawsuit claimed that the magazin had inflicted great pain by lying about the actress",
      "The hamilton colledge campus is 13,00 acres, including hiking trails and a golf course",
      "to show off, to display ostentatiously炫耀, she likes to flaunt her wealth by wearing expensive jewelry in public",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 114,
    question: "Basic",
    answer: "Basic human rights includes the right to free speech and property",
    options: [
      "pertaining to financial matters财政，the account double check the finacial books at the end of fiscal year",
      "to help or encourage, 推动，促进，提升，the treaty was designed to promote trade relations between the two nations",
      "Basic human rights includes the right to free speech and property",
      "having the agreement or support of all, 一致，A unanimous verdict couldn't be reached, as one jury member refuse to vote guilty",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 115,
    question: "Befriend",
    answer: "Justin Timberlake befriended Jimmy Fallon at a chance meeting in backstage in 2002",
    options: [
      "His affectation was just a facade he put up to hide his true self.",
      "Justin Timberlake befriended Jimmy Fallon at a chance meeting in backstage in 2002",
      "The house features an additional bedroom that could be used as guest room or an office",
      "prior to Copernicus, conventional wisdoms states that the earth is the center of universe.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 116,
    question: "Begrudge",
    answer: "Amy begrudged Jo's book so much that she destroyed it in a fit of jealousy",
    options: [
      "煽动，鼓动，plainly be constructed as incitement to violence",
      "the whole experience was completely different from what we expected",
      "Amy begrudged Jo's book so much that she destroyed it in a fit of jealousy",
      "暂时的, he can come back to work when he is feeling better, but in the interim, he should rest",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 117,
    question: "belated",
    answer: "when jahnavi forgot her mom's birthday, she sent a belated birthday gift a week later.",
    options: [
      "坚定的",
      "when jahnavi forgot her mom's birthday, she sent a belated birthday gift a week later.",
      "使遭受，使承受the lawsuit claimed that the magazin had inflicted great pain by lying about the actress",
      "Clarissa offered her condolence to Ariana for the tragic death of her hamster",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 118,
    question: "beliefs",
    answer: "Many beliefs, such as the idea that earth is flat, turn out to be wrong.",
    options: [
      "检察官",
      "Many beliefs, such as the idea that earth is flat, turn out to be wrong.",
      "professional philosophers writings often appear abstruse",
      "very important, the most crucial moments in someplace are...",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 119,
    question: "belittles",
    answer: " My guidance counselor belittled my high school record by telling me that not everybody belongs in colledge.",
    options: [
      "加快 post office expedite mail delivery",
      " My guidance counselor belittled my high school record by telling me that not everybody belongs in colledge.",
      "My contribution to the bake sale was three dozen oatmeal-raised cookies",
      "刺激to excite or rouse to action, Caffine can often stimulate us to get out of bed",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 120,
    question: "belligerent",
    answer: "The mean bully was belligerent",
    options: [
      "古董",
      "The mean bully was belligerent",
      "碎片, dropped vase shattered into a dozen fragments",
      "A venus flytrap is a carnivorous plant that it gains nutrition from the insects it traps.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 121,
    question: "beneficiary",
    answer: "A beneficiary is a person who is designed to receive the benefit of the property owned by someone else",
    options: [
      "A beneficiary is a person who is designed to receive the benefit of the property owned by someone else",
      "He told his wife everything, she is his confidant",
      "栖息地snakes perfer a sunny and dry habitat",
      "the dark clouds made him anticipate a storm",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 122,
    question: "benefit",
    answer: "One benefit of exercise is that you will have more energy throughout the day",
    options: [
      "to look at as a source of information, The handout refers to the lecture's earlier speech",
      "虚构的her imaginar friend stu is just a figment",
      "The living conditions in the country are horrible, most citizens do not have running water",
      "One benefit of exercise is that you will have more energy throughout the day",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 123,
    question: "benediction",
    answer: "In certain church services, a benediction is a particular kind of blessing.",
    options: [
      "The thief absconded with the jewels",
      "to announce officially or publicly, 宣布， she proclaimed that she would be running for student body president",
      "厌恶人类者 the misanthrope refused to join the community  for their annual holiday party",
      "In certain church services, a benediction is a particular kind of blessing.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 124,
    question: "benevolent",
    answer: "The united way, like any charity, is an benevolent organization",
    options: [
      "The united way, like any charity, is an benevolent organization",
      "粗俗的,he is a crude person",
      "浮躁",
      "to help or encourage, 推动，促进，提升，the treaty was designed to promote trade relations between the two nations",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 125,
    question: "benign",
    answer: "Charilie was worried that he had a cancer, but the lump on his leg turned out to be benign",
    options: [
      "加深的 deepening split between",
      "说教的intended to teach or educate, aesop's fables is didactic literature",
      "in a large city, there is so much activity that it is difficult to find peace and economy",
      "Charilie was worried that he had a cancer, but the lump on his leg turned out to be benign",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 126,
    question: "bilateral",
    answer: "The two countries held a bilateral meeting in a neutral location",
    options: [
      "笨拙的",
      "The house features an additional bedroom that could be used as guest room or an office",
      "he is a famous architect who designed building so that they would organically fit into their surroundings",
      "The two countries held a bilateral meeting in a neutral location",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 127,
    question: "Bilingual",
    answer: "the bilingual teacher could speak to her student both in english and spanish",
    options: [
      "打败，the thief had to admit defeat when he found the police had surrouned him",
      "with assistance from the victim, the sketch artist will adumbrate a picture of the robbery suspect",
      "Some people do not like eating foods with mushy consistency",
      "the bilingual teacher could speak to her student both in english and spanish",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 128,
    question: "bipartisan",
    answer: "the agreement between republicans and democrats was bipartisan",
    options: [
      "the agreement between republicans and democrats was bipartisan",
      "to give or supply, The tomato plant will yield a huge number of tomatoes",
      "To say that something has an amorphous shape, is a contradiction. How can a shape be shapeless",
      "长袍, I would have been a drug queen named foxy codone, if it was not for that white robed god in the sky",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 129,
    question: "brevity",
    answer: "The reader of this book may be greatful for the brevity of this story.",
    options: [
      "we often do not appreciate the best things in life until they have been taken away from us.",
      "Detectives look for concretes evidence, such as hairs and fingerprint, when solving a crime",
      "my plane will arrive at approximately 9 pm",
      "The reader of this book may be greatful for the brevity of this story.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 130,
    question: "Brief",
    answer: "We had  a brief conversation on the way out the door.",
    options: [
      "a social blunder, an embarrassing mistake, 失礼, burping after you eat it's considered a gaffe",
      "分发，分配，sb distribute sth to someplace",
      "he is a famous architect who designed building so that they would organically fit into their surroundings",
      "We had  a brief conversation on the way out the door.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 131,
    question: "broad",
    answer: "The conference featured a broad range of topics, including everything from astrology to exercise",
    options: [
      "The conference featured a broad range of topics, including everything from astrology to exercise",
      "to compete, Sheryl vied with her best friend for a promotion",
      "vild mammals or birds hunted for sport or food",
      "tending to bring together or unite, attending sports events can have a unifying effect on a community",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 132,
    question: "campus",
    answer: "The hamilton colledge campus is 13,00 acres, including hiking trails and a golf course",
    options: [
      "The hamilton colledge campus is 13,00 acres, including hiking trails and a golf course",
      "intense or passionate feelings热情, he roared with the fervor of thousands fans",
      "I hope your illness does not affect your ability to work.",
      "the shape of a thing or person轮廓,through the heavy fog, he could barely make out the form of his dear friend",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 133,
    question: "cancel",
    answer: "After Tara learned that her finace had lied to her, she decided to cancel the wedding",
    options: [
      "争吵，the white car stops, the driver jumps out, and a physical brawl ensues.",
      "短跑运动员",
      "呼吁，调用，祈求At the trial, the defendant invoked his fifth amendment right to avoid self-incrimination",
      "After Tara learned that her finace had lied to her, she decided to cancel the wedding",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 134,
    question: "candel",
    answer: "when the light went out in the apartment, mimi asked roger to light her candel so she could see",
    options: [
      "he adhere to muslim faith",
      "不合情理的，extremly wrong or bad, without a moral guide, the actions of crimainal was so unconscionable the not even his lawyer could come up with a good reason to let him go free",
      "when the light went out in the apartment, mimi asked roger to light her candel so she could see",
      "判决书",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 135,
    question: "capable",
    answer: "After studying cooking in France for ten years, she is a very capable chef",
    options: [
      "it is common knowledge that exercise is good for your health",
      "谴责 he issued a report decrying the company's plan to ...",
      "胰岛素",
      "After studying cooking in France for ten years, she is a very capable chef",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 136,
    question: "capture",
    answer: "The stray dog was captured by dogcatcher",
    options: [
      "The stray dog was captured by dogcatcher",
      "坚定的",
      "the consensus at the meeting was moving forward with the project",
      "Those who had studied anthropology were excited to see the earliest known cookbook at the museum",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 137,
    question: "cardiac",
    answer: "The patient heart stopped, the doctor said it was due to cardiac arrest",
    options: [
      "larger than common size巨大的",
      "古董",
      "The patient heart stopped, the doctor said it was due to cardiac arrest",
      "The most exciting part of the film's permiere was when the lead actress made his appearance",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 138,
    question: "carnivorous",
    answer: "A venus flytrap is a carnivorous plant that it gains nutrition from the insects it traps.",
    options: [
      "煽动，鼓动，plainly be constructed as incitement to violence",
      "A venus flytrap is a carnivorous plant that it gains nutrition from the insects it traps.",
      "分发，分配，sb distribute sth to someplace",
      "不复存在 sth is defunct",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 139,
    question: "cast",
    answer: "the fisherman cast its hook into the water, hoping for a bite",
    options: [
      "荒谬",
      "The red tuxedo was conspicuous among the classic black ones",
      "the fisherman cast its hook into the water, hoping for a bite",
      "犯规，污秽",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 140,
    question: "categories",
    answer: "the book falls several literary categories, it is both fiction and history",
    options: [
      "when the light went out in the apartment, mimi asked roger to light her candel so she could see",
      "the book falls several literary categories, it is both fiction and history",
      "After Tara learned that her finace had lied to her, she decided to cancel the wedding",
      "短跑运动员",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 141,
    question: "cause",
    answer: "the cause of my lateness was that the bus broke down and I had to work 10 blocks.",
    options: [
      "having free will，自主性, he made a voluntary decision to confess, hoping that his cooperation would reduce his punishment",
      "having the agreement or support of all, 一致，A unanimous verdict couldn't be reached, as one jury member refuse to vote guilty",
      "辩护人",
      "the cause of my lateness was that the bus broke down and I had to work 10 blocks.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 142,
    question: "cease",
    answer: "when I lost my job, my expensive night on the town ceased",
    options: [
      "评估",
      "prior to Copernicus, conventional wisdoms states that the earth is the center of universe.",
      "his main characteristic was his desire for solitude",
      "when I lost my job, my expensive night on the town ceased",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 143,
    question: "central",
    answer: "Sleep is central to strong health",
    options: [
      "A venus flytrap is a carnivorous plant that it gains nutrition from the insects it traps.",
      "Sleep is central to strong health",
      "to offer or hold out to someone for acceptance, 提供，提出，because your proffer of repayment for the movie tickets was too little, I will not buy them to you",
      "威胁Mrs. Lewis's voice sounded ominous when she told the class it was time for a little test",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 144,
    question: "certain",
    answer: "Since Rhonda only answered three of the ten questions, she was certain she had failed the exam",
    options: [
      "Since Rhonda only answered three of the ten questions, she was certain she had failed the exam",
      "臭名昭著的",
      "the fisherman cast its hook into the water, hoping for a bite",
      "Let's try not to argue over who wash dishes tonight",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 145,
    question: "certainly",
    answer: "When Alex asked her mom if they could go to the museum, she responded, certainly",
    options: [
      "When Alex asked her mom if they could go to the museum, she responded, certainly",
      "C.S. Lewis wrote the history of Narnia in his Chronicles of Narnia series",
      "After the car accident, the drivers got upset and had an altercation",
      "Justin Timberlake befriended Jimmy Fallon at a chance meeting in backstage in 2002",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 146,
    question: "change",
    answer: "Selena used to be a brunette, but she changed to blonde for summer",
    options: [
      "a fictional place that where everything is good乌托邦",
      "Selena used to be a brunette, but she changed to blonde for summer",
      "The historian referred to the annals of 10th century Egyptians to write his paper",
      "冷漠，we should never be indifferent to the suffering of others",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 147,
    question: "chant",
    answer: "The children chanted as they sang ring around the rosie",
    options: [
      "变形的deformed face",
      "equal in value, equivalent amounts of money",
      "The children chanted as they sang ring around the rosie",
      "强调",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 148,
    question: "chaotic",
    answer: "with move our home was completely chaotic, with pets, boxes, and movers all over",
    options: [
      "an introductory chapter or event, 序幕，开场白, the prologue to the play set the scene for what I was about to see",
      "with move our home was completely chaotic, with pets, boxes, and movers all over",
      "when the gardener was bit by the snake, the doctor give him an antidote to prevent the posion from taking effect",
      "煽动的，愤慨的，发炎的,The internet troll wrote inflammatory comments on the scientist's posts",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 149,
    question: "characteristic",
    answer: "his main characteristic was his desire for solitude",
    options: [
      "equal in value, equivalent amounts of money",
      "truthfulness, 真实性,The veracity of the story of yong george washington chopping down the cherry tree is questioned by serious historians",
      "his main characteristic was his desire for solitude",
      "击退,驱除，抵制",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 150,
    question: "characteristic2",
    answer: "long teeth and ears are characteristic of rabbits",
    options: [
      "牛",
      "The man was ambivalent about where to eat dinner, he couldn't decide between fish and chickens",
      "freedom from external control, The Mohegan tribe has full autonomy on its own reservation",
      "long teeth and ears are characteristic of rabbits",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 151,
    question: "chastise",
    answer: "The boss will chastise the employees for leaving early",
    options: [
      "skillful, adroit机敏的，灵巧的sb is dexterous negotiator/debater/hands",
      "细胞",
      "投掷，愤慨的说，Blackburn said last week that the man in the Coolla was waiting for his spot, and hurled insults in his direction",
      "The boss will chastise the employees for leaving early",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 152,
    question: "chronic",
    answer: "Jes couldn't play sports due to her chronic asthma",
    options: [
      "栖息地snakes perfer a sunny and dry habitat",
      "Jes couldn't play sports due to her chronic asthma",
      "标准，the criteria of this job include...",
      "The celebrity was so intimidating, I was not sure how to approach him",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 153,
    question: "chronicles",
    answer: "C.S. Lewis wrote the history of Narnia in his Chronicles of Narnia series",
    options: [
      "C.S. Lewis wrote the history of Narnia in his Chronicles of Narnia series",
      "父权社会the women linve in the patriarchy wanted to expand the votes to include them",
      "评估",
      "Swimming has always been consistent part of my life, I swim three days a week or more",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 154,
    question: "chronological",
    answer: "The biography told the story of F. Scott in chronological order from his birth in 1896 to his death in 1940.",
    options: [
      "The biography told the story of F. Scott in chronological order from his birth in 1896 to his death in 1940.",
      "The reader of this book may be greatful for the brevity of this story.",
      "不复存在 sth is defunct",
      "to underline, to emphasize, his terrible hunger underscores the importance of remembering to eat",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 155,
    question: "circuit",
    answer: "the distance around the campus is about 3 miles, so I had to complete the circuit twice to run 6 miles.",
    options: [
      "the distance around the campus is about 3 miles, so I had to complete the circuit twice to run 6 miles.",
      "The automatic dishwasher cleans the dishes without any work from the chef",
      "Romeo and Juliet is a perfect archetype of the genre",
      "假说 the science experiment proved the student's hypothesis was false",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 156,
    question: "circumspect",
    answer: "The groundhog was very circumspect as he slowly came out of his hole",
    options: [
      "The groundhog was very circumspect as he slowly came out of his hole",
      "清晰的，易读的",
      "When Alex asked her mom if they could go to the museum, she responded, certainly",
      "Molly attributed her frustration to her lack of sleep",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 157,
    question: "circumstances",
    answer: "Given my finiancial circumstances, I am not sure I should be going on vacation this summer",
    options: [
      "to take care of or look after, I am happy to tend to your plants while you are away on vacation",
      "the consensus at the meeting was moving forward with the project",
      "管道工",
      "Given my finiancial circumstances, I am not sure I should be going on vacation this summer",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 158,
    question: "circumvent",
    answer: "The angry school board circumvented the students's efforts to install televesions in ever classroom",
    options: [
      "he is an adept basketball player",
      "The angry school board circumvented the students's efforts to install televesions in ever classroom",
      "狡猾的she had a sly personality/sly sip of water",
      "The aurora borealis is usually seen in high latitude regions like the arctic, so it would be an anomaly if it were seen in New england",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 159,
    question: "clamor",
    answer: "I awoke in the middle night to a loud clamor, my neighbors were arguing again",
    options: [
      "I awoke in the middle night to a loud clamor, my neighbors were arguing again",
      "she was so artistic that even her fruit bowel arranged in a beautiful manner",
      "弃权，放弃",
      "ZIN uh foh bee uh, a fear of people from other countries, Despite his xenophobia, he packed his bags, got on the plane, and started to explore different countries",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 160,
    question: "classified",
    answer: "The ornithologist classified his birds by size, color and beak type",
    options: [
      "skillful, adroit机敏的，灵巧的sb is dexterous negotiator/debater/hands",
      "The ornithologist classified his birds by size, color and beak type",
      "to compete, Sheryl vied with her best friend for a promotion",
      "The conference featured a broad range of topics, including everything from astrology to exercise",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 161,
    question: "clearly",
    answer: "After twenty years of experience and multiple awards, she is clearly the best person for the job",
    options: [
      "the rival factions ended their war with a peace accord",
      "The family decided to abbreviate their vacation when a hurricane threatened the island",
      "After twenty years of experience and multiple awards, she is clearly the best person for the job",
      "使遭受，使承受the lawsuit claimed that the magazin had inflicted great pain by lying about the actress",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 162,
    question: "climatic",
    answer: "climatic changes have been reported in the sourthern regions, many of which have been experiencing record high temperatures",
    options: [
      "climatic changes have been reported in the sourthern regions, many of which have been experiencing record high temperatures",
      "The photographer wanted to augment her income by shooting weddings on the weekends",
      "The yankees bought the pitcher's contract for a considerable sum of money",
      "something unusual, significant, or impressive, a solar eclipse is a natural phenomenon that some people will never witness",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 163,
    question: "coincidence",
    answer: "what a coincidence, jill and todd got each other the same card for the anniversary",
    options: [
      "what a coincidence, jill and todd got each other the same card for the anniversary",
      "争吵，the white car stops, the driver jumps out, and a physical brawl ensues.",
      "The red tuxedo was conspicuous among the classic black ones",
      "the consensus at the meeting was moving forward with the project",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 164,
    question: "collide",
    answer: "one theory suggests that the grand canyon was formed when a meteor collided with the earth",
    options: [
      "煽动的，愤慨的，发炎的,The internet troll wrote inflammatory comments on the scientist's posts",
      "one theory suggests that the grand canyon was formed when a meteor collided with the earth",
      "格言警句 adage, an authoritative saying, no pain, no gain is a dictum",
      "I was asleep, but still conscious of the rain beating against the window",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 165,
    question: "combine",
    answer: "if you combine flour and water, you will get dough",
    options: [
      "if you combine flour and water, you will get dough",
      "On Valentine's day, Farhad was feeling amorous, so he took his girlfriend to a romantic dinner",
      "The celebrity was so intimidating, I was not sure how to approach him",
      "when the light went out in the apartment, mimi asked roger to light her candel so she could see",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 166,
    question: "common",
    answer: "it is common knowledge that exercise is good for your health",
    options: [
      "The reader of this book may be greatful for the brevity of this story.",
      "it is common knowledge that exercise is good for your health",
      "玷污,hate to defile it by doing sth",
      "The thief absconded with the jewels",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 167,
    question: "compare",
    answer: "If you compare the living between paris and New York, renting in paris is much cheaper",
    options: [
      "full of liquid, after getting caught in the monsoon for several hours, our clothing was soaked",
      "短跑运动员",
      "If you compare the living between paris and New York, renting in paris is much cheaper",
      "信任",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 168,
    question: "complacent",
    answer: "voters turnout is low in this city, most residents are complacent about the current state of politics",
    options: [
      "voters turnout is low in this city, most residents are complacent about the current state of politics",
      "the primary reason he took a test prep course was to raise his test scores",
      "of the most importance, principally, the town is primarily a middle-class community",
      "The reader of this book may be greatful for the brevity of this story.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 169,
    question: "completely",
    answer: "the whole experience was completely different from what we expected",
    options: [
      "the whole experience was completely different from what we expected",
      "his belligerent behavior did not follow the code of conduct",
      "they are differ in many areas: hair colors..",
      "to join together, two oxen were yoked together and hooked up to pull the plow",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 170,
    question: "complex",
    answer: "The country faced complex economic problems that stemmed from a variety of different causes.",
    options: [
      "an aggregate flower; an aggregate fruit(strawberry, raspberry, blackberry)",
      "The country faced complex economic problems that stemmed from a variety of different causes.",
      "a state of permanence, peace, or order, Having lived in four different cities in the past two years, he is now craved stability",
      "公平的 the distribution is equitable",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 171,
    question: "component",
    answer: "The component in any laptop these days is its microchip",
    options: [
      "with their soft fur and large eyes, puppies are appealing to almost everyone",
      "The component in any laptop these days is its microchip",
      "Clarissa offered her condolence to Ariana for the tragic death of her hamster",
      "可信的，the story was not credible",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 172,
    question: "compromise",
    answer: "I am an early raiser and my wife usually sleep late, so we decided to compromise and woke up at 10:00 am",
    options: [
      "The photographer wanted to augment her income by shooting weddings on the weekends",
      "I am an early raiser and my wife usually sleep late, so we decided to compromise and woke up at 10:00 am",
      "a small space, often remote or secret深处，dungeons can be found in the recesses of some castles",
      "玷污,hate to defile it by doing sth",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 173,
    question: "concede",
    answer: "the instructor would never concede that he had made a mistake in grading the exam",
    options: [
      "the instructor would never concede that he had made a mistake in grading the exam",
      "to underline, to emphasize, his terrible hunger underscores the importance of remembering to eat",
      "Our house is adjacent to the corner store",
      "pertaining to seeing, 视觉的，the film had great visual effects, such as fireballs and flying people",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 174,
    question: "concentrate",
    answer: "it is difficult to concentrate on studying when there is loud music playing",
    options: [
      "镜头,Danville Costco video Footage shows both men could have walked away, DA",
      "诡计多端的",
      "it is difficult to concentrate on studying when there is loud music playing",
      "the data represented by the scientist was accurate",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 175,
    question: "concept",
    answer: "some people find the concept to immortality difficult to understand",
    options: [
      "厌恶人类者 the misanthrope refused to join the community  for their annual holiday party",
      "折断，the tension on the rope was so tight that he was afraid it would snap at any time",
      "some people find the concept to immortality difficult to understand",
      "she has such an enthusiastic attitude the everyone enjoyed being around her",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 176,
    question: "concerned",
    answer: "I was concerned when you didn't show up for work at the usual time",
    options: [
      "when I lost my job, my expensive night on the town ceased",
      "Her persistent cough contradicts her statement that she is feeling well",
      "I was concerned when you didn't show up for work at the usual time",
      "to help or encourage, 推动，促进，提升，the treaty was designed to promote trade relations between the two nations",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 177,
    question: "conclude",
    answer: "the evening's festivities was concluded with a round of ballroom dance",
    options: [
      "the evening's festivities was concluded with a round of ballroom dance",
      "粗俗的,he is a crude person",
      "the passage from winter to spring is very abrupt",
      "able to easily carried or moved, The mini dog was portable enough to fit in her purse",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 178,
    question: "conclusion",
    answer: "it is important to understand how the historians reached this conclusion",
    options: [
      "it is important to understand how the historians reached this conclusion",
      "The groundhog was very circumspect as he slowly came out of his hole",
      "Congress was forced to compromise in order to appease the holdouts",
      "In contemporary society, cell phones and laptops are very normal",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 179,
    question: "concrete",
    answer: "Detectives look for concretes evidence, such as hairs and fingerprint, when solving a crime",
    options: [
      "strike with a firm blow, he smited the water with his sword; be strongly attracted to someone or sth, you got smitten",
      "实例in this instance i disagree",
      "the acceptance of something undesirable but inevitable, there is an resignation in Alex's voice when he announced that",
      "Detectives look for concretes evidence, such as hairs and fingerprint, when solving a crime",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 180,
    question: "conditions",
    answer: "The living conditions in the country are horrible, most citizens do not have running water",
    options: [
      "险恶的",
      "the consensus at the meeting was moving forward with the project",
      "The living conditions in the country are horrible, most citizens do not have running water",
      "半透明的",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 181,
    question: "condolence",
    answer: "Clarissa offered her condolence to Ariana for the tragic death of her hamster",
    options: [
      "Clarissa offered her condolence to Ariana for the tragic death of her hamster",
      "The crooked businessman devised many schemes to make money",
      "the state or condition of being equal, it is impossible to establish parity in grades, because...",
      "freedom from external control, The Mohegan tribe has full autonomy on its own reservation",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 182,
    question: "conducive",
    answer: "Darkness is often conducive to one's ability to sleep",
    options: [
      "Darkness is often conducive to one's ability to sleep",
      "Most kids feels pressure to conform to the standards of their peers",
      "the distance around the campus is about 3 miles, so I had to complete the circuit twice to run 6 miles.",
      "扩张，the business's expansion was impressive",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 183,
    question: "conduct",
    answer: "his belligerent behavior did not follow the code of conduct",
    options: [
      "her ability to play piano is staggering, she can play the hardest pieces effortlessly.",
      "声名狼藉的they are infamous bank robbers",
      "武断的 sb is dogmatic on sth",
      "his belligerent behavior did not follow the code of conduct",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 184,
    question: "confidant",
    answer: "He told his wife everything, she is his confidant",
    options: [
      "恶意的，恶毒的the debate turned negative when one candidate maliciously attacked the character of his opponent",
      "He told his wife everything, she is his confidant",
      "刺穿的",
      "To say that something has an amorphous shape, is a contradiction. How can a shape be shapeless",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 185,
    question: "confident",
    answer: "The politician was such a confident person that even when he was behind the polls, he was still convinced he could win",
    options: [
      "All this appears in the form of a story or fabel, called an allegory",
      "to anger, to stimulate, to cause, if you see a snake, do not provoke it or it may strike",
      "The politician was such a confident person that even when he was behind the polls, he was still convinced he could win",
      "Her background in Roman Language was helpful in her trip to Europe",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 186,
    question: "conflict",
    answer: "The conflict between the Great Britain and the colonies turned into the revolutionary war",
    options: [
      "围困",
      "To ignore these issues would be a serious abnegation of responsibility",
      "The conflict between the Great Britain and the colonies turned into the revolutionary war",
      "short trip短途旅行take a one-day excursion to sp nearby",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 187,
    question: "conform",
    answer: "Most kids feels pressure to conform to the standards of their peers",
    options: [
      "the general course or prevailing tendency, 趋势，Rose gold watches are popular jewelry trend today",
      "粗俗的,he is a crude person",
      "Most kids feels pressure to conform to the standards of their peers",
      "镜头,Danville Costco video Footage shows both men could have walked away, DA",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 188,
    question: "confuse",
    answer: "The new information only confused the situation",
    options: [
      "捐赠者 The money was raised from individual donors",
      "Some people do not like eating foods with mushy consistency",
      "The new information only confused the situation",
      "千年The epic science-fiction novel told the story of an alien society over the course of a millennium",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 189,
    question: "connected",
    answer: "Many scientists speculate that exposure to music at a young age is connected the advanced intelligence",
    options: [
      "Many scientists speculate that exposure to music at a young age is connected the advanced intelligence",
      "to spread throughout, the small of my mom's cookies is starting to pervade my room and make my mouth water",
      "excessive昂贵的，the sky-high prices were exorbitant",
      "跛行",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 190,
    question: "connection",
    answer: "there is a strong connection between salary and education level",
    options: [
      "there is a strong connection between salary and education level",
      "only the most advanced students can truly understand the fermi paradox",
      "the passage from winter to spring is very abrupt",
      "Those who had studied anthropology were excited to see the earliest known cookbook at the museum",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 191,
    question: "conscious",
    answer: "I was asleep, but still conscious of the rain beating against the window",
    options: [
      "we often do not appreciate the best things in life until they have been taken away from us.",
      "栖息地snakes perfer a sunny and dry habitat",
      "the rebirth of a soul in a new body",
      "I was asleep, but still conscious of the rain beating against the window",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 192,
    question: "consensus",
    answer: "the consensus at the meeting was moving forward with the project",
    options: [
      "the consensus at the meeting was moving forward with the project",
      "Eating snails is something that does not appeal to me",
      "providing an immediate advantage,应急之际 it is expedient to do something",
      "Our house is adjacent to the corner store",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 193,
    question: "consequences",
    answer: "Obey the rules or prepare to suffer the consequences",
    options: [
      "罪魁祸首，who is culprit?",
      "Congress was forced to compromise in order to appease the holdouts",
      "Obey the rules or prepare to suffer the consequences",
      "仪式，one of the group's religious ritual is to abstain from eating break for a week.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 194,
    question: "conservation",
    answer: "Those worried about pollution making strong arguments for the conservation of parks and green space",
    options: [
      "to reduce or take away the value of有损于 sth will not detract sb's joy/fame",
      "larger than common size巨大的",
      "there is a strong connection between salary and education level",
      "Those worried about pollution making strong arguments for the conservation of parks and green space",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 195,
    question: "consider",
    answer: "before buying a dog, you need to consider whether or not you'll be able to take care of it",
    options: [
      "only the most advanced students can truly understand the fermi paradox",
      "The automatic dishwasher cleans the dishes without any work from the chef",
      "this location is completely secure",
      "before buying a dog, you need to consider whether or not you'll be able to take care of it",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 196,
    question: "considerable",
    answer: "The yankees bought the pitcher's contract for a considerable sum of money",
    options: [
      "the book falls several literary categories, it is both fiction and history",
      "to move a sound or signal from one place to another, cellular towers transmit signals from one phone to another",
      "pertaining to seeing, 视觉的，the film had great visual effects, such as fireballs and flying people",
      "The yankees bought the pitcher's contract for a considerable sum of money",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 197,
    question: "consideration",
    answer: "The couple's daily commute was an important consideration in buying a house",
    options: [
      "to occur again, repeatedly, the headache that he got as a child recur when he eats too much ice cream",
      "I made some assumptions about Dana's character without really knowing her",
      "静脉",
      "The couple's daily commute was an important consideration in buying a house",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 198,
    question: "consistency",
    answer: "Some people do not like eating foods with mushy consistency",
    options: [
      "Some people do not like eating foods with mushy consistency",
      "pertaining to a practical point-of-view,务实,my father is always taking a pragmatic approach, reminding me to be practical instead of impulsive",
      "细读",
      "to put in a place for safekeeping,堆积，存放 deposit cash in a bank account",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 199,
    question: "consistent",
    answer: "Swimming has always been consistent part of my life, I swim three days a week or more",
    options: [
      "Swimming has always been consistent part of my life, I swim three days a week or more",
      "Many beliefs, such as the idea that earth is flat, turn out to be wrong.",
      "The united way, like any charity, is an benevolent organization",
      "His affectation was just a facade he put up to hide his true self.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 200,
    question: "consist",
    answer: "Her apartment consists of three rooms: a bedroom, a bathroom, and a kitchen",
    options: [
      "Her apartment consists of three rooms: a bedroom, a bathroom, and a kitchen",
      "煽动的，愤慨的，发炎的,The internet troll wrote inflammatory comments on the scientist's posts",
      "The mean bully was belligerent",
      "加深的 deepening split between",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 201,
    question: "consolidate",
    answer: "He consolidated his students loan and credit card debt in to one convenient payment",
    options: [
      "able to easily carried or moved, The mini dog was portable enough to fit in her purse",
      "In spite of her old age, he continued to walk miles everyday",
      "He consolidated his students loan and credit card debt in to one convenient payment",
      "Ice chips can help alleviate this symptom",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 202,
    question: "conspicuous",
    answer: "The red tuxedo was conspicuous among the classic black ones",
    options: [
      "术语， the term gridlock refers to a traffic jam in which cars cannot move",
      "检察官",
      "existing below the threshold of consciousness潜意识的,since buliminal suggestions exists beneath our concious levels of thought",
      "The red tuxedo was conspicuous among the classic black ones",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 203,
    question: "constant",
    answer: "Traffic jams are a constant source of irritation in modern life",
    options: [
      "Traffic jams are a constant source of irritation in modern life",
      "Safforn is very expensive, and is often adulterated with other plants",
      "州际公路the family drove through an interstate highway from their home in Texas to their new home Florida",
      "推断I can infer from her tan that she had vacationed in the caribbean",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 204,
    question: "constrained",
    answer: "being a raw-food vegetarian, she has a very constrained diet",
    options: [
      "being a raw-food vegetarian, she has a very constrained diet",
      "He consolidated his students loan and credit card debt in to one convenient payment",
      "In spite of her old age, he continued to walk miles everyday",
      "The skaters continuously moved around the rink all night",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 205,
    question: "construct",
    answer: "Currently, builders are eagerly to construct houses in neighborhoods with growing populations",
    options: [
      "full of liquid, after getting caught in the monsoon for several hours, our clothing was soaked",
      "千年The epic science-fiction novel told the story of an alien society over the course of a millennium",
      "Currently, builders are eagerly to construct houses in neighborhoods with growing populations",
      "to support, hold, or bear up from below, A bridge can sustain a lot of weight",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 206,
    question: "consume",
    answer: "The football players consumed so much food, that it was difficult to keep the refrigerator stocked",
    options: [
      "The historian referred to the annals of 10th century Egyptians to write his paper",
      "The football players consumed so much food, that it was difficult to keep the refrigerator stocked",
      "to depict visually or describe in words, she portrayed her boyfriend as tall, even though he was in fact short",
      "providing an immediate advantage,应急之际 it is expedient to do something",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 207,
    question: "contain",
    answer: "my purse contain tissue paper, lipstack, and day calender",
    options: [
      "my purse contain tissue paper, lipstack, and day calender",
      "加快 post office expedite mail delivery",
      "C.S. Lewis wrote the history of Narnia in his Chronicles of Narnia series",
      "初步的, it would not likely get past a preliminary hearing, and a judge could potentially criticize the office for doing sth",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 208,
    question: "contemporary",
    answer: "In contemporary society, cell phones and laptops are very normal",
    options: [
      "unusual, different from the normal standard古怪，反常的 she is quite an eccentric lady",
      "In contemporary society, cell phones and laptops are very normal",
      "traits or qualities of something, one of the properties of dry ice is that it is very cold",
      "ZIN uh foh bee uh, a fear of people from other countries, Despite his xenophobia, he packed his bags, got on the plane, and started to explore different countries",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 209,
    question: "context",
    answer: "In order to better understand history, we need to study context of certain historical event",
    options: [
      "In order to better understand history, we need to study context of certain historical event",
      "fresh, original新颖的, Ray had a novel approach to homework, he did the work before it was assigned",
      "啮齿动物",
      "On Valentine's day, Farhad was feeling amorous, so he took his girlfriend to a romantic dinner",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 210,
    question: "continue",
    answer: "In spite of her old age, he continued to walk miles everyday",
    options: [
      "She is normally calm and level headed, so this outburst is an aberration",
      "The country faced complex economic problems that stemmed from a variety of different causes.",
      "In spite of her old age, he continued to walk miles everyday",
      "干预",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 211,
    question: "continuously",
    answer: "The skaters continuously moved around the rink all night",
    options: [
      "The skaters continuously moved around the rink all night",
      "碎片, dropped vase shattered into a dozen fragments",
      "静脉",
      "One benefit of exercise is that you will have more energy throughout the day",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 212,
    question: "contradict",
    answer: "Her persistent cough contradicts her statement that she is feeling well",
    options: [
      "糖尿病患者",
      "Her persistent cough contradicts her statement that she is feeling well",
      "this location is completely secure",
      "identification with the feelings or thought of another, he feels great deal of empathy for sb's suffering",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 213,
    question: "contradiction",
    answer: "To say that something has an amorphous shape, is a contradiction. How can a shape be shapeless",
    options: [
      "the country's involvement in its neighbors affairs has caused quite a controversy",
      "tending to bring together or unite, attending sports events can have a unifying effect on a community",
      "To say that something has an amorphous shape, is a contradiction. How can a shape be shapeless",
      "威胁Mrs. Lewis's voice sounded ominous when she told the class it was time for a little test",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 214,
    question: "contraband",
    answer: "Because it is not allowed in school, student kept a secret stach of contraband candy in her locker",
    options: [
      "my plane will arrive at approximately 9 pm",
      "Because it is not allowed in school, student kept a secret stach of contraband candy in her locker",
      "标准，the criteria of this job include...",
      "pertaining to financial matters财政，the account double check the finacial books at the end of fiscal year",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 215,
    question: "contrast",
    answer: "her bright blue shoes contrast sharply with her dark red pants",
    options: [
      "投掷，愤慨的说，Blackburn said last week that the man in the Coolla was waiting for his spot, and hurled insults in his direction",
      "her bright blue shoes contrast sharply with her dark red pants",
      "The red tuxedo was conspicuous among the classic black ones",
      "to join together, two oxen were yoked together and hooked up to pull the plow",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 216,
    question: "contribute",
    answer: "Bill Gates has contributes millions of dollars to stop the spread of HIV in Africa",
    options: [
      "Bill Gates has contributes millions of dollars to stop the spread of HIV in Africa",
      "concerned with ordinary activities or business, I loved pink hat, but my more practical side won out, and I decided not to buy it",
      "this location is completely secure",
      "to spread throughout, the small of my mom's cookies is starting to pervade my room and make my mouth water",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 217,
    question: "contribution",
    answer: "My contribution to the bake sale was three dozen oatmeal-raised cookies",
    options: [
      "My contribution to the bake sale was three dozen oatmeal-raised cookies",
      "起诉，there was not enough evidence to bring prosecution on this case",
      "to represent, to portray,描绘 dipicted sth as ...",
      "刺激to excite or rouse to action, Caffine can often stimulate us to get out of bed",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 218,
    question: "controversy",
    answer: "the country's involvement in its neighbors affairs has caused quite a controversy",
    options: [
      "明目张胆的glaringly bad, notorious,the player was fined for a flagrant foul that left his opponent injured",
      "the country's involvement in its neighbors affairs has caused quite a controversy",
      "仓促的，草草的，粗略的 a cursory glance as she walked toward",
      "Her persistent cough contradicts her statement that she is feeling well",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 219,
    question: "convenient",
    answer: "we live in a convenient location, right next to a 24 hours supermarket",
    options: [
      "we live in a convenient location, right next to a 24 hours supermarket",
      "to regard with contempt蔑视, sb didained sb for sth",
      "the presidential palace was accessible only to friends and family",
      "pertaining to financial matters财政，the account double check the finacial books at the end of fiscal year",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 220,
    question: "conventional",
    answer: "prior to Copernicus, conventional wisdoms states that the earth is the center of universe.",
    options: [
      "prior to Copernicus, conventional wisdoms states that the earth is the center of universe.",
      "to come before something, smoke and loud noises preceded the volcanic eruption",
      "开脱，to free completely from blame, to exculpate开脱 the jury exonerated the accused",
      "The united way, like any charity, is an benevolent organization",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 221,
    question: "convince",
    answer: "The look on his face convinced her that he was guilty",
    options: [
      "夸张",
      "an introductory chapter or event, 序幕，开场白, the prologue to the play set the scene for what I was about to see",
      "to look at as a source of information, The handout refers to the lecture's earlier speech",
      "The look on his face convinced her that he was guilty",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 222,
    question: "correspond",
    answer: "to be in agreement, to be similar, to communicate by exchange of letters",
    options: [
      "折断，the tension on the rope was so tight that he was afraid it would snap at any time",
      "to be in agreement, to be similar, to communicate by exchange of letters",
      "a small space, often remote or secret深处，dungeons can be found in the recesses of some castles",
      "The house features an additional bedroom that could be used as guest room or an office",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 223,
    question: "cosmopolitan",
    answer: "见多识广，四海为家的人, a truly cosmopolitan traveler",
    options: [
      "武断的 sb is dogmatic on sth",
      "粗俗的,he is a crude person",
      "The biography told the story of F. Scott in chronological order from his birth in 1896 to his death in 1940.",
      "见多识广，四海为家的人, a truly cosmopolitan traveler",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 224,
    question: "credential",
    answer: "证书display the credential in a frame on the wall",
    options: [
      "不复存在 sth is defunct",
      "I made some assumptions about Dana's character without really knowing her",
      "证书display the credential in a frame on the wall",
      "无缘无故的，无端的，Danville resident who was hospitalized following the fight, told media that the fight was unprovoked",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 225,
    question: "credible",
    answer: "可信的，the story was not credible",
    options: [
      "relying on experience or observation凭经验,we empirically proved the pie's deliciousness by eatting it",
      "可信的，the story was not credible",
      "Let's try not to argue over who wash dishes tonight",
      "The conference featured a broad range of topics, including everything from astrology to exercise",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 226,
    question: "credulous",
    answer: "eager to believe,轻信的，易上当的，sb is so credulous",
    options: [
      "One benefit of exercise is that you will have more energy throughout the day",
      "she has such an enthusiastic attitude the everyone enjoyed being around her",
      "there is a strong connection between salary and education level",
      "eager to believe,轻信的，易上当的，sb is so credulous",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 227,
    question: "criteria",
    answer: "标准，the criteria of this job include...",
    options: [
      "stephen king is an accomplished writer, with over forty books to his name",
      "标准，the criteria of this job include...",
      "The stray dog was captured by dogcatcher",
      "to depict visually or describe in words, she portrayed her boyfriend as tall, even though he was in fact short",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 228,
    question: "critic",
    answer: "评论家，critics said the movie was horrible",
    options: [
      "different, incompatible,不同的 the two cultures were so utterly disparate",
      "after travel throughout the country,we settled in seattle to start a family",
      "评论家，critics said the movie was horrible",
      "Given my finiancial circumstances, I am not sure I should be going on vacation this summer",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 229,
    question: "crucial",
    answer: "very important, the most crucial moments in someplace are...",
    options: [
      "尊重 show deference to sb",
      "climatic changes have been reported in the sourthern regions, many of which have been experiencing record high temperatures",
      "争吵，the white car stops, the driver jumps out, and a physical brawl ensues.",
      "very important, the most crucial moments in someplace are...",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 230,
    question: "crude",
    answer: "粗俗的,he is a crude person",
    options: [
      "A venus flytrap is a carnivorous plant that it gains nutrition from the insects it traps.",
      "While on vacation, the students visited an amphitheater in Rome called the Colosseum",
      "起诉，there was not enough evidence to bring prosecution on this case",
      "粗俗的,he is a crude person",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 231,
    question: "culprit",
    answer: "罪魁祸首，who is culprit?",
    options: [
      "罪魁祸首，who is culprit?",
      "群居Dophins are a gregarious species of oceanic mammal",
      "He amalgamate his company with another",
      "He consolidated his students loan and credit card debt in to one convenient payment",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 232,
    question: "cursory",
    answer: "仓促的，草草的，粗略的 a cursory glance as she walked toward",
    options: [
      "amended the manuscript, amend the situation, amend a constitution",
      "the consensus at the meeting was moving forward with the project",
      "争吵，the white car stops, the driver jumps out, and a physical brawl ensues.",
      "仓促的，草草的，粗略的 a cursory glance as she walked toward",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 233,
    question: "debase",
    answer: "贬低,sb debased himself by lying to sb",
    options: [
      "贬低,sb debased himself by lying to sb",
      "瘟疫 a terrible epidemic",
      "after travel throughout the country,we settled in seattle to start a family",
      "to underline, to emphasize, his terrible hunger underscores the importance of remembering to eat",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 234,
    question: "debunk",
    answer: "揭穿to show something is not true, he debunked the company's claim that",
    options: [
      "His expert of using color and shadow made the painting an aesthetic success",
      "揭穿to show something is not true, he debunked the company's claim that",
      "She makes an adequate amount of money, but she still could not afford to go on a fancy vacation",
      "The angry school board circumvented the students's efforts to install televesions in ever classroom",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 235,
    question: "decry",
    answer: "谴责 he issued a report decrying the company's plan to ...",
    options: [
      "谴责 he issued a report decrying the company's plan to ...",
      "the agreement between republicans and democrats was bipartisan",
      "the acceptance of something undesirable but inevitable, there is an resignation in Alex's voice when he announced that",
      "I awoke in the middle night to a loud clamor, my neighbors were arguing again",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 236,
    question: "decay",
    answer: "腐烂 sugar can cause you teeth to decay",
    options: [
      "明目张胆的glaringly bad, notorious,the player was fined for a flagrant foul that left his opponent injured",
      "fulfilling all requirements, the maid's cleanup was satisfactory, but not outstanding",
      "being the most important force or component统治，主宰,dominant leader/color",
      "腐烂 sugar can cause you teeth to decay",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 237,
    question: "deepening",
    answer: "加深的 deepening split between",
    options: [
      "放大Tiny cells can be viewed through a microscope because it will magnify them to 400 times their actual size",
      "When Alex asked her mom if they could go to the museum, she responded, certainly",
      "群居Dophins are a gregarious species of oceanic mammal",
      "加深的 deepening split between",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 238,
    question: "defective",
    answer: "有缺陷的the tv was defective",
    options: [
      "to join together, two oxen were yoked together and hooked up to pull the plow",
      "The children chanted as they sang ring around the rosie",
      "Her background in Roman Language was helpful in her trip to Europe",
      "有缺陷的the tv was defective",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 239,
    question: "deference",
    answer: "尊重 show deference to sb",
    options: [
      "voters turnout is low in this city, most residents are complacent about the current state of politics",
      "different, incompatible,不同的 the two cultures were so utterly disparate",
      "If you compare the living between paris and New York, renting in paris is much cheaper",
      "尊重 show deference to sb",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 240,
    question: "defile",
    answer: "玷污,hate to defile it by doing sth",
    options: [
      "浮躁",
      "ambivalence about their goals, why our ambivalence?",
      "skillful, adroit机敏的，灵巧的sb is dexterous negotiator/debater/hands",
      "玷污,hate to defile it by doing sth",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 241,
    question: "deformed",
    answer: "变形的deformed face",
    options: [
      "群居Dophins are a gregarious species of oceanic mammal",
      "变形的deformed face",
      "诡计多端的",
      "freedom from external control, The Mohegan tribe has full autonomy on its own reservation",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 242,
    question: "defunct",
    answer: "不复存在 sth is defunct",
    options: [
      "eager to believe,轻信的，易上当的，sb is so credulous",
      "发明",
      "压迫, much like the women you are trying to oppress",
      "不复存在 sth is defunct",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 243,
    question: "degenerate",
    answer: "退化 sth/ sb is degenerated",
    options: [
      "退化 sth/ sb is degenerated",
      "使遭受，使承受the lawsuit claimed that the magazin had inflicted great pain by lying about the actress",
      "机能失调的 the dysfunctional family fought so loudly",
      "to become worse or fall apart变坏abandon house begin to deteriorate",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 244,
    question: "dense",
    answer: "稠密 a dense cluster of stars, a dense population",
    options: [
      "威胁Mrs. Lewis's voice sounded ominous when she told the class it was time for a little test",
      "稠密 a dense cluster of stars, a dense population",
      "The sound of the car alarm downstairs annoyed the residents who were trying to sleep",
      "She became adroit at dealing with difficult questions",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 245,
    question: "depend",
    answer: "children depend on their parents",
    options: [
      "children depend on their parents",
      "The most exciting part of the film's permiere was when the lead actress made his appearance",
      "规范，被认可的社会标准It is difficult to go against norms of the society",
      "投掷，愤慨的说，Blackburn said last week that the man in the Coolla was waiting for his spot, and hurled insults in his direction",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 246,
    question: "dependent",
    answer: " sb is financially dependent on sth",
    options: [
      "投掷，愤慨的说，Blackburn said last week that the man in the Coolla was waiting for his spot, and hurled insults in his direction",
      "含义，意味, when you said I looked healthy, was that really an implication that I have put on weight?",
      " sb is financially dependent on sth",
      "excessive昂贵的，the sky-high prices were exorbitant",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 247,
    question: "depict",
    answer: "to represent, to portray,描绘 dipicted sth as ...",
    options: [
      "to represent, to portray,描绘 dipicted sth as ...",
      "The family decided to abbreviate their vacation when a hurricane threatened the island",
      "The children chanted as they sang ring around the rosie",
      "freedom from external control, The Mohegan tribe has full autonomy on its own reservation",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 248,
    question: "deplete",
    answer: "to decrease the supply of, to exhaust;耗尽 deplete the oil reserves",
    options: [
      "to decrease the supply of, to exhaust;耗尽 deplete the oil reserves",
      "to escape, to avoid逃避，规避，回避 celebrity evade paparazzi on XXX",
      "Selena used to be a brunette, but she changed to blonde for summer",
      "The cactus has developed an adaptation that allows it survive without water for months at a time",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 249,
    question: "deposit",
    answer: "to put in a place for safekeeping,堆积，存放 deposit cash in a bank account",
    options: [
      "the heavy rain was an antecedent event to the flooding that occurred",
      "to put in a place for safekeeping,堆积，存放 deposit cash in a bank account",
      "the parade is an annual affair",
      "坚定的",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 250,
    question: "deride",
    answer: "to redicule, to laugh at, 嘲弄 sb deride sb's driving ability",
    options: [
      "规范，被认可的社会标准It is difficult to go against norms of the society",
      "a state of permanence, peace, or order, Having lived in four different cities in the past two years, he is now craved stability",
      "推断I can infer from her tan that she had vacationed in the caribbean",
      "to redicule, to laugh at, 嘲弄 sb deride sb's driving ability",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 251,
    question: "despite",
    answer: "prep regardless of; without being affected by, Despite her many challenges,...",
    options: [
      "概念where did you get that notion? I never said anything about it",
      "prep regardless of; without being affected by, Despite her many challenges,...",
      "he is an adept basketball player",
      "professional knowledge or skill, technical expertise",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 252,
    question: "deter",
    answer: "to discourage阻止，震慑a dog will deter thieves from ...",
    options: [
      "to discourage阻止，震慑a dog will deter thieves from ...",
      "the book falls several literary categories, it is both fiction and history",
      "it will difficult for polar bear to adapt to the changing climate",
      "clearly and directly expressed, the instruction is explicit",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 253,
    question: "deteriorate",
    answer: "to become worse or fall apart变坏abandon house begin to deteriorate",
    options: [
      "冷漠，we should never be indifferent to the suffering of others",
      "to reduce or take away the value of有损于 sth will not detract sb's joy/fame",
      "he is a famous architect who designed building so that they would organically fit into their surroundings",
      "to become worse or fall apart变坏abandon house begin to deteriorate",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 254,
    question: "detract",
    answer: "to reduce or take away the value of有损于 sth will not detract sb's joy/fame",
    options: [
      "to reduce or take away the value of有损于 sth will not detract sb's joy/fame",
      "强调",
      "判决书",
      "见多识广，四海为家的人, a truly cosmopolitan traveler",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 255,
    question: "dexterous",
    answer: "skillful, adroit机敏的，灵巧的sb is dexterous negotiator/debater/hands",
    options: [
      "skillful, adroit机敏的，灵巧的sb is dexterous negotiator/debater/hands",
      "歪，弯曲",
      "无能的笨拙的无效的, not all gamers are socially inept",
      "校内的, the intramural football league had teams made up of inhabitants at each of the university's dorms",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 256,
    question: "dictate",
    answer: "say or read aloud sb dictate sth to sb",
    options: [
      "Ice chips can help alleviate this symptom",
      "to rise in opposition to an establish ruler, The teenagers chose to rebel against the unfair dress code by wearing purple sneakers",
      "say or read aloud sb dictate sth to sb",
      "I am an early raiser and my wife usually sleep late, so we decided to compromise and woke up at 10:00 am",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 257,
    question: "dictum",
    answer: "格言警句 adage, an authoritative saying, no pain, no gain is a dictum",
    options: [
      "tending to bring together or unite, attending sports events can have a unifying effect on a community",
      "概念where did you get that notion? I never said anything about it",
      "格言警句 adage, an authoritative saying, no pain, no gain is a dictum",
      "挥霍",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 258,
    question: "didactic",
    answer: "说教的intended to teach or educate, aesop's fables is didactic literature",
    options: [
      "歪，弯曲",
      "the bilingual teacher could speak to her student both in english and spanish",
      "strike with a firm blow, he smited the water with his sword; be strongly attracted to someone or sth, you got smitten",
      "说教的intended to teach or educate, aesop's fables is didactic literature",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 259,
    question: "differ",
    answer: "they are differ in many areas: hair colors..",
    options: [
      "they are differ in many areas: hair colors..",
      "群居Dophins are a gregarious species of oceanic mammal",
      "when I lost my job, my expensive night on the town ceased",
      "变形的deformed face",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 260,
    question: "discord",
    answer: "不和谐 many causes of discord between the two people/things",
    options: [
      "children depend on their parents",
      "不和谐 many causes of discord between the two people/things",
      "贡献the wealthy business man gives a generous offering to the church",
      "狡猾的she had a sly personality/sly sip of water",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 261,
    question: "Disdain",
    answer: "to regard with contempt蔑视, sb didained sb for sth",
    options: [
      "to regard with contempt蔑视, sb didained sb for sth",
      "The minister was an altruistic man who gave the money he earned to the community",
      "He told his wife everything, she is his confidant",
      "收回，取回,retrieve or recover something that was lost, she will reclaim the dress she lent to her sister last week",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 262,
    question: "disparage",
    answer: "to belittle, 贬损 sb disparage sb by doing sth",
    options: [
      "clearly and directly expressed, the instruction is explicit",
      "to belittle, 贬损 sb disparage sb by doing sth",
      "excessive昂贵的，the sky-high prices were exorbitant",
      "宿舍",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 263,
    question: "disparate",
    answer: "different, incompatible,不同的 the two cultures were so utterly disparate",
    options: [
      "截获，侦听 The FBI intercpeted several phone calls that warned of a dangerous plot",
      "Clarissa offered her condolence to Ariana for the tragic death of her hamster",
      "the bilingual teacher could speak to her student both in english and spanish",
      "different, incompatible,不同的 the two cultures were so utterly disparate",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 264,
    question: "disperse",
    answer: "分散 police dispersed the crowd.",
    options: [
      "分散 police dispersed the crowd.",
      " sb is financially dependent on sth",
      "to underline, to emphasize, his terrible hunger underscores the importance of remembering to eat",
      "to be in agreement, to be similar, to communicate by exchange of letters",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 265,
    question: "displace",
    answer: "to compel to leave home迫使离开原地 aniamls displaced by wildfire,",
    options: [
      "If you compare the living between paris and New York, renting in paris is much cheaper",
      "I was asleep, but still conscious of the rain beating against the window",
      "to compel to leave home迫使离开原地 aniamls displaced by wildfire,",
      "悼词",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 266,
    question: "disrupt",
    answer: "扰乱 the barking dog disrupted my sleep",
    options: [
      "扰乱 the barking dog disrupted my sleep",
      "pertaining to seeing, 视觉的，the film had great visual effects, such as fireballs and flying people",
      "明显的，清晰的",
      "压迫, much like the women you are trying to oppress",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 267,
    question: "distinct",
    answer: "kim has a distinct style that only she can pull off",
    options: [
      "A beneficiary is a person who is designed to receive the benefit of the property owned by someone else",
      "Let's try not to argue over who wash dishes tonight",
      "Ice chips can help alleviate this symptom",
      "kim has a distinct style that only she can pull off",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 268,
    question: "distribute",
    answer: "分发，分配，sb distribute sth to someplace",
    options: [
      "破坏，the children's adamant refusal to learn french considerably undermines their teacher's effort",
      "击退,驱除，抵制",
      "分发，分配，sb distribute sth to someplace",
      "a small but nevertheless important change",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 269,
    question: "divert",
    answer: "转移，the police diverted traffic to a side street",
    options: [
      "发白热光的，emitting light as a result of being heated, the meteor become incandescent as it hurled toward the earth",
      "争吵，the white car stops, the driver jumps out, and a physical brawl ensues.",
      "击退,驱除，抵制",
      "转移，the police diverted traffic to a side street",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 270,
    question: "dogmatic",
    answer: "武断的 sb is dogmatic on sth",
    options: [
      "Safforn is very expensive, and is often adulterated with other plants",
      "Her background in Roman Language was helpful in her trip to Europe",
      "武断的 sb is dogmatic on sth",
      "围困",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 271,
    question: "dominant",
    answer: "being the most important force or component统治，主宰,dominant leader/color",
    options: [
      "严格,demanding",
      "弃权，放弃",
      "a state of permanence, peace, or order, Having lived in four different cities in the past two years, he is now craved stability",
      "being the most important force or component统治，主宰,dominant leader/color",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 272,
    question: "dominate",
    answer: "to rule over, to control, sb dominate sb",
    options: [
      "起诉，there was not enough evidence to bring prosecution on this case",
      "to rule over, to control, sb dominate sb",
      "扩张，the business's expansion was impressive",
      "a small but nevertheless important change",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 273,
    question: "donor",
    answer: "捐赠者 The money was raised from individual donors",
    options: [
      "渴望",
      "父权社会the women linve in the patriarchy wanted to expand the votes to include them",
      "捐赠者 The money was raised from individual donors",
      "故障，失灵The robotic vaccum cleaner worked for monthes before it started to malfunction",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 274,
    question: "dubious",
    answer: "full of doubt, 半信半疑的 Jerry's dubious claim that he could fly like superman",
    options: [
      "full of doubt, 半信半疑的 Jerry's dubious claim that he could fly like superman",
      "to regard with contempt蔑视, sb didained sb for sth",
      "In order to better understand history, we need to study context of certain historical event",
      "full of doubt, 半信半疑的 Jerry's dubious claim that he could fly like superman",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 275,
    question: "dysfunctional",
    answer: "机能失调的 the dysfunctional family fought so loudly",
    options: [
      "机能失调的 the dysfunctional family fought so loudly",
      "My contribution to the bake sale was three dozen oatmeal-raised cookies",
      "willing to obey someone else, the youngest wolves submissive to the older, stronger more experienced wolves",
      "existing below the threshold of consciousness潜意识的,since buliminal suggestions exists beneath our concious levels of thought",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 276,
    question: "dystopia",
    answer: "a fictional place where everything is bad反乌托邦 the hunger games is set in a dydtopia",
    options: [
      "to put in a place for safekeeping,堆积，存放 deposit cash in a bank account",
      "a fictional place where everything is bad反乌托邦 the hunger games is set in a dydtopia",
      "He told his wife everything, she is his confidant",
      "a part considered in relation to the whole, 比重，比例，this minor traffic accident is small in proportion to what is going on in thw world",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 277,
    question: "eccentric",
    answer: "unusual, different from the normal standard古怪，反常的 she is quite an eccentric lady",
    options: [
      "the data represented by the scientist was accurate",
      "玷污,hate to defile it by doing sth",
      "瘟疫 a terrible epidemic",
      "unusual, different from the normal standard古怪，反常的 she is quite an eccentric lady",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 278,
    question: "eloquent",
    answer: "well-spoken,有说服力的 The speaker was so eloquent",
    options: [
      "接踵而至，接着发生",
      "to give or supply, The tomato plant will yield a huge number of tomatoes",
      "the heavy rain was an antecedent event to the flooding that occurred",
      "well-spoken,有说服力的 The speaker was so eloquent",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 279,
    question: "elusive",
    answer: "hard to pin down, evasive, 难以琢磨的，困难的the answer to this question was elusive",
    options: [
      "to move a sound or signal from one place to another, cellular towers transmit signals from one phone to another",
      "华丽的beautiful, elaborate, or extravagant, the singers gave a magnificent performance",
      "hard to pin down, evasive, 难以琢磨的，困难的the answer to this question was elusive",
      "胜诉, achieving success in legal proceeding, the likelihood of prevailing in court was pretty low.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 280,
    question: "emerge",
    answer: "to come into view, often from a hidden place,出来，产生，plane emerge from the clouds",
    options: [
      "What is Akrasia and how to overcome it",
      "to come into view, often from a hidden place,出来，产生，plane emerge from the clouds",
      "睫毛膏",
      "I was concerned when you didn't show up for work at the usual time",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 281,
    question: "emergence",
    answer: "the process of emerging, appearance,出现strong emergence, emergence in physics, emergence of the internet",
    options: [
      "the rebirth of a soul in a new body",
      "The hamilton colledge campus is 13,00 acres, including hiking trails and a golf course",
      "the process of emerging, appearance,出现strong emergence, emergence in physics, emergence of the internet",
      "the act of mentioning something, At lunch, he made a reference to the fact he...",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 282,
    question: "emerging",
    answer: "coming into being,新出现的, an emerging market, cade slowly emerging from his shell",
    options: [
      "再起，复兴",
      "He consolidated his students loan and credit card debt in to one convenient payment",
      "coming into being,新出现的, an emerging market, cade slowly emerging from his shell",
      "fulfilling all requirements, the maid's cleanup was satisfactory, but not outstanding",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 283,
    question: "empathy",
    answer: "identification with the feelings or thought of another, he feels great deal of empathy for sb's suffering",
    options: [
      "well-being, happiness or health, 福利，the country provided free health coverage for the welfare of its citizens",
      "identification with the feelings or thought of another, he feels great deal of empathy for sb's suffering",
      "不合情理的，extremly wrong or bad, without a moral guide, the actions of crimainal was so unconscionable the not even his lawyer could come up with a good reason to let him go free",
      "the distance around the campus is about 3 miles, so I had to complete the circuit twice to run 6 miles.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 284,
    question: "empirically",
    answer: "relying on experience or observation凭经验,we empirically proved the pie's deliciousness by eatting it",
    options: [
      "Romeo and Juliet is a perfect archetype of the genre",
      "检察官",
      "relying on experience or observation凭经验,we empirically proved the pie's deliciousness by eatting it",
      "to reduce or take away the value of有损于 sth will not detract sb's joy/fame",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 285,
    question: "enchant",
    answer: "取悦，使陶醉, she was enchanted by the prince, it was as if he had put a spell on her",
    options: [
      "取悦，使陶醉, she was enchanted by the prince, it was as if he had put a spell on her",
      "freedom from external control, The Mohegan tribe has full autonomy on its own reservation",
      "赐给",
      "to represent, to portray,描绘 dipicted sth as ...",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 286,
    question: "enormous",
    answer: "larger than common size巨大的",
    options: [
      "Eating snails is something that does not appeal to me",
      "larger than common size巨大的",
      "to occur again, repeatedly, the headache that he got as a child recur when he eats too much ice cream",
      "Given my finiancial circumstances, I am not sure I should be going on vacation this summer",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 287,
    question: "epidemic",
    answer: "瘟疫 a terrible epidemic",
    options: [
      "able to be seen, on a clear day, mount hood is visible from most locations in portland",
      "瘟疫 a terrible epidemic",
      "扩张，the business's expansion was impressive",
      "the heavy rain was an antecedent event to the flooding that occurred",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 288,
    question: "ephemeral",
    answer: "短暂的flowers are ephemeral",
    options: [
      "规范，被认可的社会标准It is difficult to go against norms of the society",
      "it will difficult for polar bear to adapt to the changing climate",
      "change or exchange, the governor's shift in opinions was unexpected",
      "短暂的flowers are ephemeral",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 289,
    question: "equitable",
    answer: "公平的 the distribution is equitable",
    options: [
      "we want an outdoor wedding, but we have an alternative locations if it rains",
      "公平的 the distribution is equitable",
      "if you combine flour and water, you will get dough",
      "associated with the country life, I love big citys, but sometimes I crave the peace and solitude of rural life",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 290,
    question: "equivalent",
    answer: "equal in value, equivalent amounts of money",
    options: [
      "unable to be avoided, conflict is inevitable in even the happiest of marriage",
      "评论家，critics said the movie was horrible",
      "equal in value, equivalent amounts of money",
      "牛",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 291,
    question: "estimate",
    answer: "评估",
    options: [
      "分散 police dispersed the crowd.",
      "Because it is not allowed in school, student kept a secret stach of contraband candy in her locker",
      "评估",
      "异想天开，诙谐的，怪诞的，determined by chance or impulse, the author turned out to be just as whimsical as the playful and amusing character in her book",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 292,
    question: "eulogy",
    answer: "悼词",
    options: [
      "不复存在 sth is defunct",
      "君主制 the british monarchy has sustatined for amlmost a millennium",
      "悼词",
      "投掷，愤慨的说，Blackburn said last week that the man in the Coolla was waiting for his spot, and hurled insults in his direction",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 293,
    question: "euphemism",
    answer: "委婉语 one euphemism is to say xxx instead of xxx",
    options: [
      "多产的, he wrote prolifically, having completed three novels in the past year",
      "Some people do not like eating foods with mushy consistency",
      "委婉语 one euphemism is to say xxx instead of xxx",
      "one of the many advantages of living in the country is that the air is cleaner",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 294,
    question: "evade",
    answer: "to escape, to avoid逃避，规避，回避 celebrity evade paparazzi on XXX",
    options: [
      "her ability to play piano is staggering, she can play the hardest pieces effortlessly.",
      " My guidance counselor belittled my high school record by telling me that not everybody belongs in colledge.",
      "to escape, to avoid逃避，规避，回避 celebrity evade paparazzi on XXX",
      "After years being under Soviet rule, Lithuania finally became an autonomous nation in 1900 ",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 295,
    question: "exacting",
    answer: "requiring careful attention to detail or skill严苛的he has a very exacting standards",
    options: [
      "requiring careful attention to detail or skill严苛的he has a very exacting standards",
      "悼词",
      "to offer or hold out to someone for acceptance, 提供，提出，because your proffer of repayment for the movie tickets was too little, I will not buy them to you",
      "奢华的,spend freely, bestow generously, to squander, city hall has lavished money on the street cleaning program",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 296,
    question: "exclaim",
    answer: "to cry out with sudden emotion, often in pain or surprise惊呼sb exclaimed at something",
    options: [
      "his main characteristic was his desire for solitude",
      "Her persistent cough contradicts her statement that she is feeling well",
      "to cry out with sudden emotion, often in pain or surprise惊呼sb exclaimed at something",
      "监控，surveillance footage(监控镜头)shows two men fighting following a likely verbal altercation in the costco parking lot",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 297,
    question: "excursion",
    answer: "short trip短途旅行take a one-day excursion to sp nearby",
    options: [
      "unusual, different from the normal standard古怪，反常的 she is quite an eccentric lady",
      "short trip短途旅行take a one-day excursion to sp nearby",
      "石板的教师，the pedagogue in charge of my history class refused to let us change seats, because",
      "to move a sound or signal from one place to another, cellular towers transmit signals from one phone to another",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 298,
    question: "exonerate",
    answer: "开脱，to free completely from blame, to exculpate开脱 the jury exonerated the accused",
    options: [
      "The crooked businessman devised many schemes to make money",
      "发明",
      "开脱，to free completely from blame, to exculpate开脱 the jury exonerated the accused",
      "to put in a place for safekeeping,堆积，存放 deposit cash in a bank account",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 299,
    question: "exorbitant",
    answer: "excessive昂贵的，the sky-high prices were exorbitant",
    options: [
      "a stupid or foolish person, you are shithead bozo",
      "excessive昂贵的，the sky-high prices were exorbitant",
      "the whole experience was completely different from what we expected",
      "仪式，one of the group's religious ritual is to abstain from eating break for a week.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 300,
    question: "expansion",
    answer: "扩张，the business's expansion was impressive",
    options: [
      "扩张，the business's expansion was impressive",
      "煽动的，愤慨的，发炎的,The internet troll wrote inflammatory comments on the scientist's posts",
      "不显眼的the witness saw everything, but the thief wore inconspicuous jeans, so she was not sure how to describe him to the police",
      "I was asleep, but still conscious of the rain beating against the window",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 301,
    question: "expedient",
    answer: "providing an immediate advantage,应急之际 it is expedient to do something",
    options: [
      "a part considered in relation to the whole, 比重，比例，this minor traffic accident is small in proportion to what is going on in thw world",
      "The paster has authority to marry the couple",
      "the country's involvement in its neighbors affairs has caused quite a controversy",
      "providing an immediate advantage,应急之际 it is expedient to do something",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 302,
    question: "expedite",
    answer: "加快 post office expedite mail delivery",
    options: [
      "凶猛的",
      "加快 post office expedite mail delivery",
      "to think about or relfect on without necessary evidence, Since she refuses to answer my questions, we can only speculate as to what her true motives were",
      "I hope your illness does not affect your ability to work.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 303,
    question: "expend",
    answer: "to use up花费expend financial resources on sth",
    options: [
      "召集，召开",
      "news reporter, Blackburn told the patch he is now declining to comments on the advice of his attorneys",
      "to use up花费expend financial resources on sth",
      "The boy who broke the lamp wasn't the boy who was punished, it was frustratingly arbitrary",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 304,
    question: "expertise",
    answer: "professional knowledge or skill, technical expertise",
    options: [
      "Her persistent cough contradicts her statement that she is feeling well",
      "professional knowledge or skill, technical expertise",
      "pertaining to a practical point-of-view,务实,my father is always taking a pragmatic approach, reminding me to be practical instead of impulsive",
      "I made some assumptions about Dana's character without really knowing her",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 305,
    question: "explicit",
    answer: "clearly and directly expressed, the instruction is explicit",
    options: [
      "clearly and directly expressed, the instruction is explicit",
      "武断的 sb is dogmatic on sth",
      "Sara gave an ambiguous answer to the lawyer's question",
      "Are there any foods that you abhor?",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 306,
    question: "extremes",
    answer: "the two ends of range, death valley has great extremes of heat and cold",
    options: [
      "to rise in opposition to an establish ruler, The teenagers chose to rebel against the unfair dress code by wearing purple sneakers",
      "虚构的her imaginar friend stu is just a figment",
      "to decrease the supply of, to exhaust;耗尽 deplete the oil reserves",
      "the two ends of range, death valley has great extremes of heat and cold",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 307,
    question: "fervor",
    answer: "intense or passionate feelings热情, he roared with the fervor of thousands fans",
    options: [
      "栖息地snakes perfer a sunny and dry habitat",
      "to use up花费expend financial resources on sth",
      "intense or passionate feelings热情, he roared with the fervor of thousands fans",
      "She makes an adequate amount of money, but she still could not afford to go on a fancy vacation",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 308,
    question: "figment",
    answer: "虚构的her imaginar friend stu is just a figment",
    options: [
      "虚构的her imaginar friend stu is just a figment",
      "to decrease the supply of, to exhaust;耗尽 deplete the oil reserves",
      "having free will，自主性, he made a voluntary decision to confess, hoping that his cooperation would reduce his punishment",
      "不朽，不死,the vampire is mythical creature that is usually described as immortal",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 309,
    question: "fiscal",
    answer: "pertaining to financial matters财政，the account double check the finacial books at the end of fiscal year",
    options: [
      "The couple's daily commute was an important consideration in buying a house",
      "he is an adept basketball player",
      "to reduce or take away the value of有损于 sth will not detract sb's joy/fame",
      "pertaining to financial matters财政，the account double check the finacial books at the end of fiscal year",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 310,
    question: "flagrant",
    answer: "明目张胆的glaringly bad, notorious,the player was fined for a flagrant foul that left his opponent injured",
    options: [
      "The united way, like any charity, is an benevolent organization",
      "The living conditions in the country are horrible, most citizens do not have running water",
      "Since Rhonda only answered three of the ten questions, she was certain she had failed the exam",
      "明目张胆的glaringly bad, notorious,the player was fined for a flagrant foul that left his opponent injured",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 311,
    question: "flaunt",
    answer: "to show off, to display ostentatiously炫耀, she likes to flaunt her wealth by wearing expensive jewelry in public",
    options: [
      "The living conditions in the country are horrible, most citizens do not have running water",
      "to show off, to display ostentatiously炫耀, she likes to flaunt her wealth by wearing expensive jewelry in public",
      "校内的, the intramural football league had teams made up of inhabitants at each of the university's dorms",
      "to become worse or fall apart变坏abandon house begin to deteriorate",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 312,
    question: "foreshadow",
    answer: "to serve as a warning or prediction伏笔,the dark clouds foreshadow a great storm apporaching",
    options: [
      "voters turnout is low in this city, most residents are complacent about the current state of politics",
      "to serve as a warning or prediction伏笔,the dark clouds foreshadow a great storm apporaching",
      "the process by which sth is made, prevent the formation of fungus",
      "石板的教师，the pedagogue in charge of my history class refused to let us change seats, because",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 313,
    question: "form",
    answer: "the shape of a thing or person轮廓,through the heavy fog, he could barely make out the form of his dear friend",
    options: [
      "睫毛膏",
      "the shape of a thing or person轮廓,through the heavy fog, he could barely make out the form of his dear friend",
      "leaning toward a particular kind of thought or action, 倾向, he has a tendency to want to walk the longer way home from school",
      "收回，取回,retrieve or recover something that was lost, she will reclaim the dress she lent to her sister last week",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 314,
    question: "formation",
    answer: "the process by which sth is made, prevent the formation of fungus",
    options: [
      "the process by which sth is made, prevent the formation of fungus",
      "监控，surveillance footage(监控镜头)shows two men fighting following a likely verbal altercation in the costco parking lot",
      "The house features an additional bedroom that could be used as guest room or an office",
      "future generations, decendants, samantha is saving her diaries for posterity, she hopes that her daughters enjoys them",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 315,
    question: "fragment",
    answer: "碎片, dropped vase shattered into a dozen fragments",
    options: [
      "呼吁，调用，祈求At the trial, the defendant invoked his fifth amendment right to avoid self-incrimination",
      "The house features an additional bedroom that could be used as guest room or an office",
      "假说 the science experiment proved the student's hypothesis was false",
      "碎片, dropped vase shattered into a dozen fragments",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 316,
    question: "gaffe",
    answer: "a social blunder, an embarrassing mistake, 失礼, burping after you eat it's considered a gaffe",
    options: [
      "The hamilton colledge campus is 13,00 acres, including hiking trails and a golf course",
      "a social blunder, an embarrassing mistake, 失礼, burping after you eat it's considered a gaffe",
      "there is a strong connection between salary and education level",
      "湿透的，she liked how inexpensive she's umbrella was, up untill it's poor quality left her drenched in the rain",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 317,
    question: "gregarious",
    answer: "群居Dophins are a gregarious species of oceanic mammal",
    options: [
      "初步的, it would not likely get past a preliminary hearing, and a judge could potentially criticize the office for doing sth",
      "君主制 the british monarchy has sustatined for amlmost a millennium",
      "群居Dophins are a gregarious species of oceanic mammal",
      "long teeth and ears are characteristic of rabbits",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 318,
    question: "habitat",
    answer: "栖息地snakes perfer a sunny and dry habitat",
    options: [
      "The minister was an altruistic man who gave the money he earned to the community",
      "栖息地snakes perfer a sunny and dry habitat",
      "the rebirth of a soul in a new body",
      "one of the many advantages of living in the country is that the air is cleaner",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 319,
    question: "harmony",
    answer: "agreement or congruence和谐we are unable to live together in harmony",
    options: [
      "a social blunder, an embarrassing mistake, 失礼, burping after you eat it's considered a gaffe",
      "agreement or congruence和谐we are unable to live together in harmony",
      "When the recluse died, his vast art collection was auctioned to raise money for community",
      "with their soft fur and large eyes, puppies are appealing to almost everyone",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 320,
    question: "Hyperbole",
    answer: "夸张，example of hyperbole, I am so hungry, I could eat a house",
    options: [
      "强调",
      "本土的",
      "to represent, to portray,描绘 dipicted sth as ...",
      "夸张，example of hyperbole, I am so hungry, I could eat a house",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 321,
    question: "hypothesis",
    answer: "假说 the science experiment proved the student's hypothesis was false",
    options: [
      "the whole experience was completely different from what we expected",
      "假说 the science experiment proved the student's hypothesis was false",
      "Clarissa offered her condolence to Ariana for the tragic death of her hamster",
      "vild mammals or birds hunted for sport or food",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 322,
    question: "immortal",
    answer: "不朽，不死,the vampire is mythical creature that is usually described as immortal",
    options: [
      "不朽，不死,the vampire is mythical creature that is usually described as immortal",
      "it is common knowledge that exercise is good for your health",
      "to give or supply, The tomato plant will yield a huge number of tomatoes",
      "分散 police dispersed the crowd.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 323,
    question: "impede",
    answer: "阻碍missing his front teeth impede his ability to speak clearly",
    options: [
      "in a large city, there is so much activity that it is difficult to find peace and economy",
      "阻碍missing his front teeth impede his ability to speak clearly",
      "When the recluse died, his vast art collection was auctioned to raise money for community",
      "When Alex asked her mom if they could go to the museum, she responded, certainly",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 324,
    question: "imperative",
    answer: "至关重要,the children didn't think clean up playroom is imperative",
    options: [
      "the parade is an annual affair",
      "至关重要,the children didn't think clean up playroom is imperative",
      "夸张，example of hyperbole, I am so hungry, I could eat a house",
      "分发，分配，sb distribute sth to someplace",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 325,
    question: "implication",
    answer: "含义，意味, when you said I looked healthy, was that really an implication that I have put on weight?",
    options: [
      "含义，意味, when you said I looked healthy, was that really an implication that I have put on weight?",
      "they are differ in many areas: hair colors..",
      "解释her interpretation of my dream suggested that I was scared of something",
      "something unusual, significant, or impressive, a solar eclipse is a natural phenomenon that some people will never witness",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 326,
    question: "incandescent",
    answer: "发白热光的，emitting light as a result of being heated, the meteor become incandescent as it hurled toward the earth",
    options: [
      "to look at as a source of information, The handout refers to the lecture's earlier speech",
      "荒谬",
      "发白热光的，emitting light as a result of being heated, the meteor become incandescent as it hurled toward the earth",
      "larger than common size巨大的",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 327,
    question: "inconspicuous",
    answer: "不显眼的the witness saw everything, but the thief wore inconspicuous jeans, so she was not sure how to describe him to the police",
    options: [
      "检察官",
      "The new information only confused the situation",
      "无缘无故的，无端的，Danville resident who was hospitalized following the fight, told media that the fight was unprovoked",
      "不显眼的the witness saw everything, but the thief wore inconspicuous jeans, so she was not sure how to describe him to the police",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 328,
    question: "incredulous",
    answer: "unwilling o believe, 难以置信的, he was at first incredulous, but he eventually came to accept the truth about...",
    options: [
      "to look at as a source of information, The handout refers to the lecture's earlier speech",
      "The cactus has developed an adaptation that allows it survive without water for months at a time",
      "his belligerent behavior did not follow the code of conduct",
      "unwilling o believe, 难以置信的, he was at first incredulous, but he eventually came to accept the truth about...",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 329,
    question: "indifferent",
    answer: "冷漠，we should never be indifferent to the suffering of others",
    options: [
      "All this appears in the form of a story or fabel, called an allegory",
      "Darkness is often conducive to one's ability to sleep",
      "he adhere to muslim faith",
      "冷漠，we should never be indifferent to the suffering of others",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 330,
    question: "inevitable",
    answer: "unable to be avoided, conflict is inevitable in even the happiest of marriage",
    options: [
      "The cactus has developed an adaptation that allows it survive without water for months at a time",
      "to compel to leave home迫使离开原地 aniamls displaced by wildfire,",
      "to become worse or fall apart变坏abandon house begin to deteriorate",
      "unable to be avoided, conflict is inevitable in even the happiest of marriage",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 331,
    question: "inept",
    answer: "无能的笨拙的无效的, not all gamers are socially inept",
    options: [
      "to occur again, repeatedly, the headache that he got as a child recur when he eats too much ice cream",
      "证书display the credential in a frame on the wall",
      "one of the many advantages of living in the country is that the air is cleaner",
      "无能的笨拙的无效的, not all gamers are socially inept",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 332,
    question: "infamous",
    answer: "声名狼藉的they are infamous bank robbers",
    options: [
      "声名狼藉的they are infamous bank robbers",
      "some people find the concept to immortality difficult to understand",
      "发白热光的，emitting light as a result of being heated, the meteor become incandescent as it hurled toward the earth",
      "The crooked businessman devised many schemes to make money",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 333,
    question: "infer",
    answer: "推断I can infer from her tan that she had vacationed in the caribbean",
    options: [
      "推断I can infer from her tan that she had vacationed in the caribbean",
      "地牢",
      "父权社会the women linve in the patriarchy wanted to expand the votes to include them",
      "fulfilling all requirements, the maid's cleanup was satisfactory, but not outstanding",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 334,
    question: "inflammatory",
    answer: "煽动的，愤慨的，发炎的,The internet troll wrote inflammatory comments on the scientist's posts",
    options: [
      "煽动的，愤慨的，发炎的,The internet troll wrote inflammatory comments on the scientist's posts",
      "not complete, we have only partial understanding of our universal",
      "clearly defined or exact, the doctor gave the patient specific instructions to take the medication only at night",
      "揭穿to show something is not true, he debunked the company's claim that",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 335,
    question: "inflict",
    answer: "使遭受，使承受the lawsuit claimed that the magazin had inflicted great pain by lying about the actress",
    options: [
      "the dark clouds made him anticipate a storm",
      "接踵而至，接着发生",
      "使遭受，使承受the lawsuit claimed that the magazin had inflicted great pain by lying about the actress",
      "long teeth and ears are characteristic of rabbits",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 336,
    question: "inhabitant",
    answer: "栖息地，the inhabitant of the ocean depths often look like fictional creatures",
    options: [
      "intense or passionate feelings热情, he roared with the fervor of thousands fans",
      "贡献the wealthy business man gives a generous offering to the church",
      "The automatic dishwasher cleans the dishes without any work from the chef",
      "栖息地，the inhabitant of the ocean depths often look like fictional creatures",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 337,
    question: "inhabit",
    answer: "to live on/in, the family inhabit a small house on a tree-lined street",
    options: [
      "长袍, I would have been a drug queen named foxy codone, if it was not for that white robed god in the sky",
      "to shrink, 枯萎, the flower withered and died when the plant was left without water a month",
      "After studying cooking in France for ten years, she is a very capable chef",
      "to live on/in, the family inhabit a small house on a tree-lined street",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 338,
    question: "instance",
    answer: "实例in this instance i disagree",
    options: [
      "徘徊,we lingered at the beach well after sunset",
      "full of doubt, 半信半疑的 Jerry's dubious claim that he could fly like superman",
      "实例in this instance i disagree",
      "加深的 deepening split between",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 339,
    question: "intercept",
    answer: "截获，侦听 The FBI intercpeted several phone calls that warned of a dangerous plot",
    options: [
      "pertaining to seeing, 视觉的，the film had great visual effects, such as fireballs and flying people",
      "截获，侦听 The FBI intercpeted several phone calls that warned of a dangerous plot",
      " My guidance counselor belittled my high school record by telling me that not everybody belongs in colledge.",
      "The ornithologist classified his birds by size, color and beak type",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 340,
    question: "interim",
    answer: "暂时的, he can come back to work when he is feeling better, but in the interim, he should rest",
    options: [
      "ZIN uh foh bee uh, a fear of people from other countries, Despite his xenophobia, he packed his bags, got on the plane, and started to explore different countries",
      "暂时的, he can come back to work when he is feeling better, but in the interim, he should rest",
      "扰乱 the barking dog disrupted my sleep",
      "capable of living,可行的, the plans for the skyscraper are viable; construction will begin immediately",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 341,
    question: "interpretation",
    answer: "解释her interpretation of my dream suggested that I was scared of something",
    options: [
      "解释her interpretation of my dream suggested that I was scared of something",
      "The most exciting part of the film's permiere was when the lead actress made his appearance",
      "not complete, we have only partial understanding of our universal",
      "The paster has authority to marry the couple",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 342,
    question: "interstate",
    answer: "州际公路the family drove through an interstate highway from their home in Texas to their new home Florida",
    options: [
      "Congress was forced to compromise in order to appease the holdouts",
      "州际公路the family drove through an interstate highway from their home in Texas to their new home Florida",
      "含义，意味, when you said I looked healthy, was that really an implication that I have put on weight?",
      "the geologist was hoping to accumulate more rock specimens on his trip out west",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 343,
    question: "intramural",
    answer: "校内的, the intramural football league had teams made up of inhabitants at each of the university's dorms",
    options: [
      "If you compare the living between paris and New York, renting in paris is much cheaper",
      "Most kids feels pressure to conform to the standards of their peers",
      "校内的, the intramural football league had teams made up of inhabitants at each of the university's dorms",
      "有缺陷的the tv was defective",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 344,
    question: "invoke",
    answer: "呼吁，调用，祈求At the trial, the defendant invoked his fifth amendment right to avoid self-incrimination",
    options: [
      " My guidance counselor belittled my high school record by telling me that not everybody belongs in colledge.",
      "呼吁，调用，祈求At the trial, the defendant invoked his fifth amendment right to avoid self-incrimination",
      "providing an immediate advantage,应急之际 it is expedient to do something",
      "My contribution to the bake sale was three dozen oatmeal-raised cookies",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 345,
    question: "lavish",
    answer: "奢华的,spend freely, bestow generously, to squander, city hall has lavished money on the street cleaning program",
    options: [
      "检察官",
      "奢华的,spend freely, bestow generously, to squander, city hall has lavished money on the street cleaning program",
      "truthfulness, 真实性,The veracity of the story of yong george washington chopping down the cherry tree is questioned by serious historians",
      "equal in value, equivalent amounts of money",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 346,
    question: "lecture",
    answer: "训斥,to criticize someone's actions, the teacher had to lecture the students about the merit of being on time",
    options: [
      "训斥,to criticize someone's actions, the teacher had to lecture the students about the merit of being on time",
      "there is a strong connection between salary and education level",
      "you must assess the effort you have put in to the task",
      "to live on/in, the family inhabit a small house on a tree-lined street",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 347,
    question: "linger",
    answer: "徘徊,we lingered at the beach well after sunset",
    options: [
      "to regard with contempt蔑视, sb didained sb for sth",
      "细读",
      "煽动的，愤慨的，发炎的,The internet troll wrote inflammatory comments on the scientist's posts",
      "徘徊,we lingered at the beach well after sunset",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 348,
    question: "magnificent",
    answer: "华丽的beautiful, elaborate, or extravagant, the singers gave a magnificent performance",
    options: [
      "华丽的beautiful, elaborate, or extravagant, the singers gave a magnificent performance",
      "糖尿病患者",
      "complete distance around the shape,周长, the security guard patrolled the perimeter of the property to ensure...",
      "my purse contain tissue paper, lipstack, and day calender",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 349,
    question: "magnify",
    answer: "放大Tiny cells can be viewed through a microscope because it will magnify them to 400 times their actual size",
    options: [
      "to establish the truth, or validity of, there is little evidence to prove you claim that you were in the shower during the crime",
      "放大Tiny cells can be viewed through a microscope because it will magnify them to 400 times their actual size",
      "弃权，放弃",
      "having free will，自主性, he made a voluntary decision to confess, hoping that his cooperation would reduce his punishment",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 350,
    question: "malfunciton",
    answer: "故障，失灵The robotic vaccum cleaner worked for monthes before it started to malfunction",
    options: [
      "故障，失灵The robotic vaccum cleaner worked for monthes before it started to malfunction",
      "news reporter, Blackburn told the patch he is now declining to comments on the advice of his attorneys",
      "说教的intended to teach or educate, aesop's fables is didactic literature",
      "His expert of using color and shadow made the painting an aesthetic success",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 351,
    question: "maliciously",
    answer: "恶意的，恶毒的the debate turned negative when one candidate maliciously attacked the character of his opponent",
    options: [
      "饥荒",
      "明目张胆的glaringly bad, notorious,the player was fined for a flagrant foul that left his opponent injured",
      "pertaining to one's sense of right and wrong, the senator made the moral decision not to accept the money from the lobbyist",
      "恶意的，恶毒的the debate turned negative when one candidate maliciously attacked the character of his opponent",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 352,
    question: "matriarchy",
    answer: "女权制The amazonian tribe of  female warriors was ruled by matriarchy",
    options: [
      "女权制The amazonian tribe of  female warriors was ruled by matriarchy",
      "to look at as a source of information, The handout refers to the lecture's earlier speech",
      "In certain church services, a benediction is a particular kind of blessing.",
      "some people find the concept to immortality difficult to understand",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 353,
    question: "millennium",
    answer: "千年The epic science-fiction novel told the story of an alien society over the course of a millennium",
    options: [
      "千年The epic science-fiction novel told the story of an alien society over the course of a millennium",
      "associated with the country life, I love big citys, but sometimes I crave the peace and solitude of rural life",
      "The couple's daily commute was an important consideration in buying a house",
      "清晰的，易读的",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 354,
    question: "minute",
    answer: "very small, The baby spider was so minute that one could barely see them",
    options: [
      "very small, The baby spider was so minute that one could barely see them",
      "评估",
      "one theory suggests that the grand canyon was formed when a meteor collided with the earth",
      "a fictional place that where everything is good乌托邦",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 355,
    question: "misanthrope",
    answer: "厌恶人类者 the misanthrope refused to join the community  for their annual holiday party",
    options: [
      "The biography told the story of F. Scott in chronological order from his birth in 1896 to his death in 1940.",
      "Soldiers need to be aware of potential danger at all times, even when they least expect it.",
      "厌恶人类者 the misanthrope refused to join the community  for their annual holiday party",
      "细胞",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 356,
    question: "momentum",
    answer: "动量，气势，force or speed of movement, momentum caused the car to coast down the hill",
    options: [
      "动量，气势，force or speed of movement, momentum caused the car to coast down the hill",
      "news reporter, Blackburn told the patch he is now declining to comments on the advice of his attorneys",
      "her ability to play piano is staggering, she can play the hardest pieces effortlessly.",
      "梳妆台",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 357,
    question: "monarchy",
    answer: "君主制 the british monarchy has sustatined for amlmost a millennium",
    options: [
      "唤醒",
      " My guidance counselor belittled my high school record by telling me that not everybody belongs in colledge.",
      "to take care of or look after, I am happy to tend to your plants while you are away on vacation",
      "君主制 the british monarchy has sustatined for amlmost a millennium",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 358,
    question: "moral",
    answer: "pertaining to one's sense of right and wrong, the senator made the moral decision not to accept the money from the lobbyist",
    options: [
      "we often do not appreciate the best things in life until they have been taken away from us.",
      "pertaining to one's sense of right and wrong, the senator made the moral decision not to accept the money from the lobbyist",
      "不合情理的，extremly wrong or bad, without a moral guide, the actions of crimainal was so unconscionable the not even his lawyer could come up with a good reason to let him go free",
      "笨拙的",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 359,
    question: "nevertheless",
    answer: "a small but nevertheless important change",
    options: [
      "the parade is an annual affair",
      "a small but nevertheless important change",
      "complete distance around the shape,周长, the security guard patrolled the perimeter of the property to ensure...",
      "a small but nevertheless important change",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 360,
    question: "nondescript",
    answer: "形容不出的，普通的难以归类的the house on the street were so nondescript, that it was hard to tell which is my friend's",
    options: [
      "动量，气势，force or speed of movement, momentum caused the car to coast down the hill",
      "形容不出的，普通的难以归类的the house on the street were so nondescript, that it was hard to tell which is my friend's",
      "concerned with ordinary activities or business, I loved pink hat, but my more practical side won out, and I decided not to buy it",
      "to redicule, to laugh at, 嘲弄 sb deride sb's driving ability",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 361,
    question: "norms",
    answer: "规范，被认可的社会标准It is difficult to go against norms of the society",
    options: [
      "规范，被认可的社会标准It is difficult to go against norms of the society",
      "the two ends of range, death valley has great extremes of heat and cold",
      "夸张，example of hyperbole, I am so hungry, I could eat a house",
      "One benefit of exercise is that you will have more energy throughout the day",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 362,
    question: "notion",
    answer: "概念where did you get that notion? I never said anything about it",
    options: [
      "her bright blue shoes contrast sharply with her dark red pants",
      "to escape, to avoid逃避，规避，回避 celebrity evade paparazzi on XXX",
      "有缺陷的the tv was defective",
      "概念where did you get that notion? I never said anything about it",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 363,
    question: "novel",
    answer: "fresh, original新颖的, Ray had a novel approach to homework, he did the work before it was assigned",
    options: [
      "严格,demanding",
      "pertaining to financial matters财政，the account double check the finacial books at the end of fiscal year",
      "the athlete was proud to accept the olympic gold medal",
      "fresh, original新颖的, Ray had a novel approach to homework, he did the work before it was assigned",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 364,
    question: "novice",
    answer: "新手The doctor had just graduated medical school, and was a novice in the emergency room",
    options: [
      "折断，the tension on the rope was so tight that he was afraid it would snap at any time",
      "Congress was forced to compromise in order to appease the holdouts",
      "新手The doctor had just graduated medical school, and was a novice in the emergency room",
      "to represent, to portray,描绘 dipicted sth as ...",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 365,
    question: "objective",
    answer: "the objective of us is to maintain the world peace",
    options: [
      "pertaining to seeing, 视觉的，the film had great visual effects, such as fireballs and flying people",
      "the objective of us is to maintain the world peace",
      "The country faced complex economic problems that stemmed from a variety of different causes.",
      "the data represented by the scientist was accurate",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 366,
    question: "offering",
    answer: "贡献the wealthy business man gives a generous offering to the church",
    options: [
      "to belittle, 贬损 sb disparage sb by doing sth",
      "when jahnavi forgot her mom's birthday, she sent a belated birthday gift a week later.",
      "贡献the wealthy business man gives a generous offering to the church",
      "strike with a firm blow, he smited the water with his sword; be strongly attracted to someone or sth, you got smitten",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 367,
    question: "ominous",
    answer: "威胁Mrs. Lewis's voice sounded ominous when she told the class it was time for a little test",
    options: [
      "威胁Mrs. Lewis's voice sounded ominous when she told the class it was time for a little test",
      "After twenty years of experience and multiple awards, she is clearly the best person for the job",
      "the distance around the campus is about 3 miles, so I had to complete the circuit twice to run 6 miles.",
      "精明的he is a shrewd person and he is shrewd enough",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 368,
    question: "pacify",
    answer: "to appease or soothe, the beleaguered general tried to pacify his fierce attacker by sending him a flower",
    options: [
      "The look on his face convinced her that he was guilty",
      "my plane will arrive at approximately 9 pm",
      "to appease or soothe, the beleaguered general tried to pacify his fierce attacker by sending him a flower",
      "the golden retreiver was amiable, she excitedly greeted every person he saw",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 369,
    question: "parity",
    answer: "the state or condition of being equal, it is impossible to establish parity in grades, because...",
    options: [
      "The yankees bought the pitcher's contract for a considerable sum of money",
      "the fisherman cast its hook into the water, hoping for a bite",
      "existing perpetually without change",
      "the state or condition of being equal, it is impossible to establish parity in grades, because...",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 370,
    question: "partial",
    answer: "not complete, we have only partial understanding of our universal",
    options: [
      "the consensus at the meeting was moving forward with the project",
      "not complete, we have only partial understanding of our universal",
      "one theory suggests that the grand canyon was formed when a meteor collided with the earth",
      "威胁Mrs. Lewis's voice sounded ominous when she told the class it was time for a little test",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 371,
    question: "patriarchy",
    answer: "父权社会the women linve in the patriarchy wanted to expand the votes to include them",
    options: [
      "amended the manuscript, amend the situation, amend a constitution",
      "unwilling o believe, 难以置信的, he was at first incredulous, but he eventually came to accept the truth about...",
      "父权社会the women linve in the patriarchy wanted to expand the votes to include them",
      "Ice chips can help alleviate this symptom",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 372,
    question: "pedagogue",
    answer: "石板的教师，the pedagogue in charge of my history class refused to let us change seats, because",
    options: [
      "His affectation was just a facade he put up to hide his true self.",
      "After studying cooking in France for ten years, she is a very capable chef",
      "to announce officially or publicly, 宣布， she proclaimed that she would be running for student body president",
      "石板的教师，the pedagogue in charge of my history class refused to let us change seats, because",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 373,
    question: "penetrate",
    answer: "穿透，to pass through, enter, or pierce, the doc waited for the needle to penetrate the vein",
    options: [
      "不复存在 sth is defunct",
      "to live on/in, the family inhabit a small house on a tree-lined street",
      "发明",
      "穿透，to pass through, enter, or pierce, the doc waited for the needle to penetrate the vein",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 374,
    question: "perimeter",
    answer: "complete distance around the shape,周长, the security guard patrolled the perimeter of the property to ensure...",
    options: [
      "Eating snails is something that does not appeal to me",
      "扩张，the business's expansion was impressive",
      "胎儿，speaking of fetuses, we are late for Lil nas x's baby shower",
      "complete distance around the shape,周长, the security guard patrolled the perimeter of the property to ensure...",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 375,
    question: "periphery",
    answer: "the outside edge of something, if the football across the periphery of the goal line, it is considered a touchdown",
    options: [
      "The old woman required assistance when getting in and out of cars",
      "the outside edge of something, if the football across the periphery of the goal line, it is considered a touchdown",
      "After twenty years of experience and multiple awards, she is clearly the best person for the job",
      "改革，how about fighting against gun reform laws that could prevent school shootings",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 376,
    question: "permanently",
    answer: "existing perpetually without change",
    options: [
      "existing perpetually without change",
      "she was a tireless advocate for peace",
      "When the recluse died, his vast art collection was auctioned to raise money for community",
      "暂定的，实验，made or done as a trial, experiment, or attempt, unsure, uncertain, these plans are tentative, we may change them at a later time",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 377,
    question: "pervade",
    answer: "to spread throughout, the small of my mom's cookies is starting to pervade my room and make my mouth water",
    options: [
      "to belittle, 贬损 sb disparage sb by doing sth",
      "a fictional place that where everything is good乌托邦",
      "to spread throughout, the small of my mom's cookies is starting to pervade my room and make my mouth water",
      "the shape of a thing or person轮廓,through the heavy fog, he could barely make out the form of his dear friend",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 378,
    question: "phenomenon",
    answer: "something unusual, significant, or impressive, a solar eclipse is a natural phenomenon that some people will never witness",
    options: [
      "精明的he is a shrewd person and he is shrewd enough",
      "The shoes I wanted to order from the store are, unfortunately, no longer available",
      "if you combine flour and water, you will get dough",
      "something unusual, significant, or impressive, a solar eclipse is a natural phenomenon that some people will never witness",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 379,
    question: "philanthropy",
    answer: "love of mankind, he domonstrated philanthropy by cooking and serving meals to the less fortunate",
    options: [
      "in a large city, there is so much activity that it is difficult to find peace and economy",
      "love of mankind, he domonstrated philanthropy by cooking and serving meals to the less fortunate",
      "After twenty years of experience and multiple awards, she is clearly the best person for the job",
      "to look at as a source of information, The handout refers to the lecture's earlier speech",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 380,
    question: "portable",
    answer: "able to easily carried or moved, The mini dog was portable enough to fit in her purse",
    options: [
      "the students were ambitious, they wanted to learn everything the school could teach them",
      "able to easily carried or moved, The mini dog was portable enough to fit in her purse",
      "信任",
      "分发，分配，sb distribute sth to someplace",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 381,
    question: "portray",
    answer: "to depict visually or describe in words, she portrayed her boyfriend as tall, even though he was in fact short",
    options: [
      "镜头,Danville Costco video Footage shows both men could have walked away, DA",
      "加深的 deepening split between",
      "to depict visually or describe in words, she portrayed her boyfriend as tall, even though he was in fact short",
      "the passage from winter to spring is very abrupt",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 382,
    question: "posses",
    answer: "to join the photograph club, you must posses a high-quality, black and write camera",
    options: [
      "the hokey player had several artificial teeth to replace the ones he had lost during the season",
      "宿舍",
      "to join the photograph club, you must posses a high-quality, black and write camera",
      "A beneficiary is a person who is designed to receive the benefit of the property owned by someone else",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 383,
    question: "posterity",
    answer: "future generations, decendants, samantha is saving her diaries for posterity, she hopes that her daughters enjoys them",
    options: [
      "future generations, decendants, samantha is saving her diaries for posterity, she hopes that her daughters enjoys them",
      "格言警句 adage, an authoritative saying, no pain, no gain is a dictum",
      "加快 post office expedite mail delivery",
      "清晰的，易读的",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 384,
    question: "practical",
    answer: "concerned with ordinary activities or business, I loved pink hat, but my more practical side won out, and I decided not to buy it",
    options: [
      "My contribution to the bake sale was three dozen oatmeal-raised cookies",
      "concerned with ordinary activities or business, I loved pink hat, but my more practical side won out, and I decided not to buy it",
      "The component in any laptop these days is its microchip",
      "before buying a dog, you need to consider whether or not you'll be able to take care of it",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 385,
    question: "pragmatic",
    answer: "pertaining to a practical point-of-view,务实,my father is always taking a pragmatic approach, reminding me to be practical instead of impulsive",
    options: [
      "We had  a brief conversation on the way out the door.",
      "to escape, to avoid逃避，规避，回避 celebrity evade paparazzi on XXX",
      "pertaining to a practical point-of-view,务实,my father is always taking a pragmatic approach, reminding me to be practical instead of impulsive",
      "existing perpetually without change",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 386,
    question: "preamble",
    answer: "the beginning of a document or introductory statement, 前言，导言，序言, the preamble to the school board meeting stated that they would disscuss some...",
    options: [
      "解释her interpretation of my dream suggested that I was scared of something",
      "Her background in Roman Language was helpful in her trip to Europe",
      "to decrease the supply of, to exhaust;耗尽 deplete the oil reserves",
      "the beginning of a document or introductory statement, 前言，导言，序言, the preamble to the school board meeting stated that they would disscuss some...",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 387,
    question: "precede",
    answer: "to come before something, smoke and loud noises preceded the volcanic eruption",
    options: [
      "adv for the most part; almost entirely, 几乎，in 1983, Tom Cruise was virtually known outside his small group of friends",
      "转移，the police diverted traffic to a side street",
      "见多识广，四海为家的人, a truly cosmopolitan traveler",
      "to come before something, smoke and loud noises preceded the volcanic eruption",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 388,
    question: "precedent",
    answer: "an earlier occurrence of something similar, the school set a precedent that all students could dye their hair unusual color by allowing ont student to do so ",
    options: [
      "to use up花费expend financial resources on sth",
      "击退,驱除，抵制",
      "再起，复兴",
      "an earlier occurrence of something similar, the school set a precedent that all students could dye their hair unusual color by allowing ont student to do so ",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 389,
    question: "preserve",
    answer: "to maintain or keep alive, in order to preserve fresh bread, make sure to keep it in dark, air-tight place",
    options: [
      "The historian referred to the annals of 10th century Egyptians to write his paper",
      "to maintain or keep alive, in order to preserve fresh bread, make sure to keep it in dark, air-tight place",
      "not enough, very little, During the great famine in Ireland, food was scarce that many people died of starvation",
      "the book falls several literary categories, it is both fiction and history",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 390,
    question: "prevalent",
    answer: "common or widespread, cell phones are so prevalent in Italy, that many people no longer use land lines",
    options: [
      "捐赠者 The money was raised from individual donors",
      "Jes couldn't play sports due to her chronic asthma",
      "common or widespread, cell phones are so prevalent in Italy, that many people no longer use land lines",
      "amended the manuscript, amend the situation, amend a constitution",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 391,
    question: "primarily",
    answer: "of the most importance, principally, the town is primarily a middle-class community",
    options: [
      "规范，被认可的社会标准It is difficult to go against norms of the society",
      "of the most importance, principally, the town is primarily a middle-class community",
      "when the light went out in the apartment, mimi asked roger to light her candel so she could see",
      "to represent, to portray,描绘 dipicted sth as ...",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 392,
    question: "primary",
    answer: "the primary reason he took a test prep course was to raise his test scores",
    options: [
      "the time at which something is most powerful, his career is now at its zenith",
      "the primary reason he took a test prep course was to raise his test scores",
      "半透明的",
      "便携式摄像机, we offer wide range of product from camcorders to flat-screen TVs",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 393,
    question: "proclaim",
    answer: "to announce officially or publicly, 宣布， she proclaimed that she would be running for student body president",
    options: [
      "to announce officially or publicly, 宣布， she proclaimed that she would be running for student body president",
      "Soldiers need to be aware of potential danger at all times, even when they least expect it.",
      "宿舍",
      " sb is financially dependent on sth",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 394,
    question: "proffer",
    answer: "to offer or hold out to someone for acceptance, 提供，提出，because your proffer of repayment for the movie tickets was too little, I will not buy them to you",
    options: [
      "吉祥的",
      "to offer or hold out to someone for acceptance, 提供，提出，because your proffer of repayment for the movie tickets was too little, I will not buy them to you",
      "The angry school board circumvented the students's efforts to install televesions in ever classroom",
      "Her apartment consists of three rooms: a bedroom, a bathroom, and a kitchen",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 395,
    question: "proficient",
    answer: "skilled in doing something, 精通, she is so proficient at her martial art that she was able to best her sensei",
    options: [
      "The shoes I wanted to order from the store are, unfortunately, no longer available",
      "古董",
      "至关重要,the children didn't think clean up playroom is imperative",
      "skilled in doing something, 精通, she is so proficient at her martial art that she was able to best her sensei",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 396,
    question: "profound",
    answer: "going beyond what is on the surface, deep,深刻的，深入的，she gave us a profound understanding of human life",
    options: [
      "he adhere to muslim faith",
      "The living conditions in the country are horrible, most citizens do not have running water",
      "going beyond what is on the surface, deep,深刻的，深入的，she gave us a profound understanding of human life",
      "Many scientists speculate that exposure to music at a young age is connected the advanced intelligence",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 397,
    question: "prolifically",
    answer: "多产的, he wrote prolifically, having completed three novels in the past year",
    options: [
      "relying on experience or observation凭经验,we empirically proved the pie's deliciousness by eatting it",
      "千年The epic science-fiction novel told the story of an alien society over the course of a millennium",
      "they are differ in many areas: hair colors..",
      "多产的, he wrote prolifically, having completed three novels in the past year",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 398,
    question: "prologue",
    answer: "an introductory chapter or event, 序幕，开场白, the prologue to the play set the scene for what I was about to see",
    options: [
      "an introductory chapter or event, 序幕，开场白, the prologue to the play set the scene for what I was about to see",
      "粗俗的,he is a crude person",
      "to help or encourage, 推动，促进，提升，the treaty was designed to promote trade relations between the two nations",
      "the students were ambitious, they wanted to learn everything the school could teach them",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 399,
    question: "promote",
    answer: "to help or encourage, 推动，促进，提升，the treaty was designed to promote trade relations between the two nations",
    options: [
      "Amy begrudged Jo's book so much that she destroyed it in a fit of jealousy",
      "The celebrity was so intimidating, I was not sure how to approach him",
      "to help or encourage, 推动，促进，提升，the treaty was designed to promote trade relations between the two nations",
      "饥荒",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 400,
    question: "properties",
    answer: "traits or qualities of something, one of the properties of dry ice is that it is very cold",
    options: [
      "traits or qualities of something, one of the properties of dry ice is that it is very cold",
      "召集，召开",
      "In spite of her old age, he continued to walk miles everyday",
      "糖尿病患者",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 401,
    question: "proportion",
    answer: "a part considered in relation to the whole, 比重，比例，this minor traffic accident is small in proportion to what is going on in thw world",
    options: [
      "说教的intended to teach or educate, aesop's fables is didactic literature",
      "providing an immediate advantage,应急之际 it is expedient to do something",
      "My contribution to the bake sale was three dozen oatmeal-raised cookies",
      "a part considered in relation to the whole, 比重，比例，this minor traffic accident is small in proportion to what is going on in thw world",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 402,
    question: "propose",
    answer: "提议",
    options: [
      "提议",
      "The house features an additional bedroom that could be used as guest room or an office",
      "The red tuxedo was conspicuous among the classic black ones",
      "The two countries held a bilateral meeting in a neutral location",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 403,
    question: "prove",
    answer: "to establish the truth, or validity of, there is little evidence to prove you claim that you were in the shower during the crime",
    options: [
      "to establish the truth, or validity of, there is little evidence to prove you claim that you were in the shower during the crime",
      "Currently, builders are eagerly to construct houses in neighborhoods with growing populations",
      "华丽的beautiful, elaborate, or extravagant, the singers gave a magnificent performance",
      "the use of rotary phone in the modern world is considered anachronistic",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 404,
    question: "provoke",
    answer: "to anger, to stimulate, to cause, if you see a snake, do not provoke it or it may strike",
    options: [
      "to anger, to stimulate, to cause, if you see a snake, do not provoke it or it may strike",
      "饥荒",
      "强调",
      "to support, hold, or bear up from below, A bridge can sustain a lot of weight",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 405,
    question: "rebel",
    answer: "to rise in opposition to an establish ruler, The teenagers chose to rebel against the unfair dress code by wearing purple sneakers",
    options: [
      "to rise in opposition to an establish ruler, The teenagers chose to rebel against the unfair dress code by wearing purple sneakers",
      "收回，取回,retrieve or recover something that was lost, she will reclaim the dress she lent to her sister last week",
      "the fisherman cast its hook into the water, hoping for a bite",
      "to live on/in, the family inhabit a small house on a tree-lined street",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 406,
    question: "recess",
    answer: "a small space, often remote or secret深处，dungeons can be found in the recesses of some castles",
    options: [
      "leaning toward a particular kind of thought or action, 倾向, he has a tendency to want to walk the longer way home from school",
      "校内的, the intramural football league had teams made up of inhabitants at each of the university's dorms",
      "a small space, often remote or secret深处，dungeons can be found in the recesses of some castles",
      "in a large city, there is so much activity that it is difficult to find peace and economy",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 407,
    question: "reclaim",
    answer: "收回，取回,retrieve or recover something that was lost, she will reclaim the dress she lent to her sister last week",
    options: [
      "She roses with alacrity and moved away",
      "to depict visually or describe in words, she portrayed her boyfriend as tall, even though he was in fact short",
      "栖息地snakes perfer a sunny and dry habitat",
      "收回，取回,retrieve or recover something that was lost, she will reclaim the dress she lent to her sister last week",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 408,
    question: "recur",
    answer: "to occur again, repeatedly, the headache that he got as a child recur when he eats too much ice cream",
    options: [
      "the dark clouds made him anticipate a storm",
      "it will difficult for polar bear to adapt to the changing climate",
      "we often do not appreciate the best things in life until they have been taken away from us.",
      "to occur again, repeatedly, the headache that he got as a child recur when he eats too much ice cream",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 409,
    question: "reduction",
    answer: "an amount that is taken away from something, A reduction in the number of wolves in YellowStone park led to a resurgence of buffalo in that area",
    options: [
      "栖息地，the inhabitant of the ocean depths often look like fictional creatures",
      "an amount that is taken away from something, A reduction in the number of wolves in YellowStone park led to a resurgence of buffalo in that area",
      "The united way, like any charity, is an benevolent organization",
      "The couple's daily commute was an important consideration in buying a house",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 410,
    question: "reference",
    answer: "the act of mentioning something, At lunch, he made a reference to the fact he...",
    options: [
      "clearly defined or exact, the doctor gave the patient specific instructions to take the medication only at night",
      "All this appears in the form of a story or fabel, called an allegory",
      "She is normally calm and level headed, so this outburst is an aberration",
      "the act of mentioning something, At lunch, he made a reference to the fact he...",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 411,
    question: "refer",
    answer: "to look at as a source of information, The handout refers to the lecture's earlier speech",
    options: [
      "fulfilling all requirements, the maid's cleanup was satisfactory, but not outstanding",
      "the instructor would never concede that he had made a mistake in grading the exam",
      "to look at as a source of information, The handout refers to the lecture's earlier speech",
      "to come into view, often from a hidden place,出来，产生，plane emerge from the clouds",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 412,
    question: "regulate",
    answer: "to control/direct by a rule, Diabetics often use insulin to regulate their suger blood",
    options: [
      "to control/direct by a rule, Diabetics often use insulin to regulate their suger blood",
      "to go beyond, she has surpass her original weight lifting goal of 250 pounds",
      "aggregate number of unemployed",
      "an emotion or attitude, the general sentiment about adding the building downtown was negative",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 413,
    question: "reincarnation",
    answer: "the rebirth of a soul in a new body",
    options: [
      "the hokey player had several artificial teeth to replace the ones he had lost during the season",
      "very small, The baby spider was so minute that one could barely see them",
      "破坏，the children's adamant refusal to learn french considerably undermines their teacher's effort",
      "the rebirth of a soul in a new body",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 414,
    question: "resignation",
    answer: "the acceptance of something undesirable but inevitable, there is an resignation in Alex's voice when he announced that",
    options: [
      "the acceptance of something undesirable but inevitable, there is an resignation in Alex's voice when he announced that",
      "武断的 sb is dogmatic on sth",
      "浮躁",
      "Her persistent cough contradicts her statement that she is feeling well",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 415,
    question: "ritual",
    answer: "仪式，one of the group's religious ritual is to abstain from eating break for a week.",
    options: [
      "格言警句 adage, an authoritative saying, no pain, no gain is a dictum",
      "clearly defined or exact, the doctor gave the patient specific instructions to take the medication only at night",
      "仪式，one of the group's religious ritual is to abstain from eating break for a week.",
      "to rule over, to control, sb dominate sb",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 416,
    question: "rural",
    answer: "associated with the country life, I love big citys, but sometimes I crave the peace and solitude of rural life",
    options: [
      "not enough, very little, During the great famine in Ireland, food was scarce that many people died of starvation",
      "Some people do not like eating foods with mushy consistency",
      "they are differ in many areas: hair colors..",
      "associated with the country life, I love big citys, but sometimes I crave the peace and solitude of rural life",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 417,
    question: "satisfactory",
    answer: "fulfilling all requirements, the maid's cleanup was satisfactory, but not outstanding",
    options: [
      "fulfilling all requirements, the maid's cleanup was satisfactory, but not outstanding",
      "校内的, the intramural football league had teams made up of inhabitants at each of the university's dorms",
      "to control/direct by a rule, Diabetics often use insulin to regulate their suger blood",
      "One benefit of exercise is that you will have more energy throughout the day",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 418,
    question: "scarce",
    answer: "not enough, very little, During the great famine in Ireland, food was scarce that many people died of starvation",
    options: [
      "The ornithologist classified his birds by size, color and beak type",
      "not enough, very little, During the great famine in Ireland, food was scarce that many people died of starvation",
      "悼词",
      "fresh, original新颖的, Ray had a novel approach to homework, he did the work before it was assigned",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 419,
    question: "scheme",
    answer: "The crooked businessman devised many schemes to make money",
    options: [
      "The crooked businessman devised many schemes to make money",
      "the rival factions ended their war with a peace accord",
      "The conflict between the Great Britain and the colonies turned into the revolutionary war",
      "associated with the country life, I love big citys, but sometimes I crave the peace and solitude of rural life",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 420,
    question: "secure",
    answer: "this location is completely secure",
    options: [
      "On Valentine's day, Farhad was feeling amorous, so he took his girlfriend to a romantic dinner",
      "this location is completely secure",
      "children depend on their parents",
      "新手The doctor had just graduated medical school, and was a novice in the emergency room",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 421,
    question: "setiment",
    answer: "an emotion or attitude, the general sentiment about adding the building downtown was negative",
    options: [
      "故障，失灵The robotic vaccum cleaner worked for monthes before it started to malfunction",
      "罪魁祸首，who is culprit?",
      "an emotion or attitude, the general sentiment about adding the building downtown was negative",
      "说教的intended to teach or educate, aesop's fables is didactic literature",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 422,
    question: "settle",
    answer: "after travel throughout the country,we settled in seattle to start a family",
    options: [
      " sb is financially dependent on sth",
      "管道工",
      "he is an amateur at golf, he had only hit a ball with the club at once",
      "after travel throughout the country,we settled in seattle to start a family",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 423,
    question: "shift",
    answer: "change or exchange, the governor's shift in opinions was unexpected",
    options: [
      "牛",
      "change or exchange, the governor's shift in opinions was unexpected",
      "very important, the most crucial moments in someplace are...",
      "with their soft fur and large eyes, puppies are appealing to almost everyone",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 424,
    question: "soaked",
    answer: "full of liquid, after getting caught in the monsoon for several hours, our clothing was soaked",
    options: [
      "Safforn is very expensive, and is often adulterated with other plants",
      "When Alex asked her mom if they could go to the museum, she responded, certainly",
      "to join together, two oxen were yoked together and hooked up to pull the plow",
      "full of liquid, after getting caught in the monsoon for several hours, our clothing was soaked",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 425,
    question: "specific",
    answer: "clearly defined or exact, the doctor gave the patient specific instructions to take the medication only at night",
    options: [
      "clearly and directly expressed, the instruction is explicit",
      "to serve as a warning or prediction伏笔,the dark clouds foreshadow a great storm apporaching",
      "clearly defined or exact, the doctor gave the patient specific instructions to take the medication only at night",
      "无缘无故的，无端的，Danville resident who was hospitalized following the fight, told media that the fight was unprovoked",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 426,
    question: "speculate",
    answer: "to think about or relfect on without necessary evidence, Since she refuses to answer my questions, we can only speculate as to what her true motives were",
    options: [
      "提议",
      "The yankees bought the pitcher's contract for a considerable sum of money",
      "to think about or relfect on without necessary evidence, Since she refuses to answer my questions, we can only speculate as to what her true motives were",
      "动量，气势，force or speed of movement, momentum caused the car to coast down the hill",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 427,
    question: "squander",
    answer: "挥霍",
    options: [
      "If you compare the living between paris and New York, renting in paris is much cheaper",
      "The crooked businessman devised many schemes to make money",
      "挥霍",
      "明目张胆的glaringly bad, notorious,the player was fined for a flagrant foul that left his opponent injured",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 428,
    question: "stability",
    answer: "a state of permanence, peace, or order, Having lived in four different cities in the past two years, he is now craved stability",
    options: [
      "to offer or hold out to someone for acceptance, 提供，提出，because your proffer of repayment for the movie tickets was too little, I will not buy them to you",
      "a state of permanence, peace, or order, Having lived in four different cities in the past two years, he is now craved stability",
      "The new information only confused the situation",
      "说客",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 429,
    question: "stimulate",
    answer: "刺激to excite or rouse to action, Caffine can often stimulate us to get out of bed",
    options: [
      "刺激to excite or rouse to action, Caffine can often stimulate us to get out of bed",
      "Given that you hate crowds, I assumed you wouldn't want my extra tickets for the concert tonight",
      "阴谋",
      "with assistance from the victim, the sketch artist will adumbrate a picture of the robbery suspect",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 430,
    question: "subliminal",
    answer: "existing below the threshold of consciousness潜意识的,since buliminal suggestions exists beneath our concious levels of thought",
    options: [
      "it is difficult to concentrate on studying when there is loud music playing",
      "existing below the threshold of consciousness潜意识的,since buliminal suggestions exists beneath our concious levels of thought",
      "to put in a place for safekeeping,堆积，存放 deposit cash in a bank account",
      "On Valentine's day, Farhad was feeling amorous, so he took his girlfriend to a romantic dinner",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 431,
    question: "submissive",
    answer: "willing to obey someone else, the youngest wolves submissive to the older, stronger more experienced wolves",
    options: [
      "willing to obey someone else, the youngest wolves submissive to the older, stronger more experienced wolves",
      "谴责 he issued a report decrying the company's plan to ...",
      "agreement or congruence和谐we are unable to live together in harmony",
      "A venus flytrap is a carnivorous plant that it gains nutrition from the insects it traps.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 432,
    question: "substantiate",
    answer: "to prove, to verify, to confirm,证实 the prosecutor did her best to substaintiate the charge against the defendant.",
    options: [
      "equal in value, equivalent amounts of money",
      "to prove, to verify, to confirm,证实 the prosecutor did her best to substaintiate the charge against the defendant.",
      "The wealthy benefactor wished to remain anonymous; she didn't want anyone to know her name",
      "the use of rotary phone in the modern world is considered anachronistic",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 433,
    question: "summon",
    answer: "to call upon for specified action, 召唤，to call upon for specified action, my friend summoned me in her locker to show me her new book",
    options: [
      "to prove, to verify, to confirm,证实 the prosecutor did her best to substaintiate the charge against the defendant.",
      "to call upon for specified action, 召唤，to call upon for specified action, my friend summoned me in her locker to show me her new book",
      "开脱，to free completely from blame, to exculpate开脱 the jury exonerated the accused",
      "信任",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 434,
    question: "surpass",
    answer: "to go beyond, she has surpass her original weight lifting goal of 250 pounds",
    options: [
      "to go beyond, she has surpass her original weight lifting goal of 250 pounds",
      "an aggregate flower; an aggregate fruit(strawberry, raspberry, blackberry)",
      "strike with a firm blow, he smited the water with his sword; be strongly attracted to someone or sth, you got smitten",
      "very important, the most crucial moments in someplace are...",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 435,
    question: "sustain",
    answer: "to support, hold, or bear up from below, A bridge can sustain a lot of weight",
    options: [
      "to support, hold, or bear up from below, A bridge can sustain a lot of weight",
      "The historian referred to the annals of 10th century Egyptians to write his paper",
      "不合情理的，extremly wrong or bad, without a moral guide, the actions of crimainal was so unconscionable the not even his lawyer could come up with a good reason to let him go free",
      "the geologist was hoping to accumulate more rock specimens on his trip out west",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 436,
    question: "tend",
    answer: "to take care of or look after, I am happy to tend to your plants while you are away on vacation",
    options: [
      "无能的笨拙的无效的, not all gamers are socially inept",
      "to take care of or look after, I am happy to tend to your plants while you are away on vacation",
      "收回，取回,retrieve or recover something that was lost, she will reclaim the dress she lent to her sister last week",
      "严格,demanding",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 437,
    question: "tendency",
    answer: "leaning toward a particular kind of thought or action, 倾向, he has a tendency to want to walk the longer way home from school",
    options: [
      "leaning toward a particular kind of thought or action, 倾向, he has a tendency to want to walk the longer way home from school",
      "The conflict between the Great Britain and the colonies turned into the revolutionary war",
      "to be in agreement, to be similar, to communicate by exchange of letters",
      "you must assess the effort you have put in to the task",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 438,
    question: "tentative",
    answer: "暂定的，实验，made or done as a trial, experiment, or attempt, unsure, uncertain, these plans are tentative, we may change them at a later time",
    options: [
      "The paster has authority to marry the couple",
      "暂定的，实验，made or done as a trial, experiment, or attempt, unsure, uncertain, these plans are tentative, we may change them at a later time",
      "to appease or soothe, the beleaguered general tried to pacify his fierce attacker by sending him a flower",
      "The president's speech was an address to congress",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 439,
    question: "term",
    answer: "术语， the term gridlock refers to a traffic jam in which cars cannot move",
    options: [
      "capable of living,可行的, the plans for the skyscraper are viable; construction will begin immediately",
      "when the gardener was bit by the snake, the doctor give him an antidote to prevent the posion from taking effect",
      "父权社会the women linve in the patriarchy wanted to expand the votes to include them",
      "术语， the term gridlock refers to a traffic jam in which cars cannot move",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 440,
    question: "transmit",
    answer: "to move a sound or signal from one place to another, cellular towers transmit signals from one phone to another",
    options: [
      "On Valentine's day, Farhad was feeling amorous, so he took his girlfriend to a romantic dinner",
      "女权制The amazonian tribe of  female warriors was ruled by matriarchy",
      "to move a sound or signal from one place to another, cellular towers transmit signals from one phone to another",
      "Traffic jams are a constant source of irritation in modern life",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 441,
    question: "trend",
    answer: "the general course or prevailing tendency, 趋势，Rose gold watches are popular jewelry trend today",
    options: [
      "the general course or prevailing tendency, 趋势，Rose gold watches are popular jewelry trend today",
      "The skaters continuously moved around the rink all night",
      "agreement or congruence和谐we are unable to live together in harmony",
      "there is a strong connection between salary and education level",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 442,
    question: "unanimous",
    answer: "having the agreement or support of all, 一致，A unanimous verdict couldn't be reached, as one jury member refuse to vote guilty",
    options: [
      "having the agreement or support of all, 一致，A unanimous verdict couldn't be reached, as one jury member refuse to vote guilty",
      "Swimming has always been consistent part of my life, I swim three days a week or more",
      "召集，召开",
      "The look on his face convinced her that he was guilty",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 443,
    question: "unconscionable",
    answer: "不合情理的，extremly wrong or bad, without a moral guide, the actions of crimainal was so unconscionable the not even his lawyer could come up with a good reason to let him go free",
    options: [
      "the students were ambitious, they wanted to learn everything the school could teach them",
      "罪魁祸首，who is culprit?",
      "of the most importance, principally, the town is primarily a middle-class community",
      "不合情理的，extremly wrong or bad, without a moral guide, the actions of crimainal was so unconscionable the not even his lawyer could come up with a good reason to let him go free",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 444,
    question: "undermine",
    answer: "破坏，the children's adamant refusal to learn french considerably undermines their teacher's effort",
    options: [
      "professional knowledge or skill, technical expertise",
      "破坏，the children's adamant refusal to learn french considerably undermines their teacher's effort",
      "便携式摄像机, we offer wide range of product from camcorders to flat-screen TVs",
      "The cactus has developed an adaptation that allows it survive without water for months at a time",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 445,
    question: "underscore",
    answer: "to underline, to emphasize, his terrible hunger underscores the importance of remembering to eat",
    options: [
      "the students were ambitious, they wanted to learn everything the school could teach them",
      "短暂的flowers are ephemeral",
      "a small but nevertheless important change",
      "to underline, to emphasize, his terrible hunger underscores the importance of remembering to eat",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 446,
    question: "unifying",
    answer: "tending to bring together or unite, attending sports events can have a unifying effect on a community",
    options: [
      "professional knowledge or skill, technical expertise",
      "in a large city, there is so much activity that it is difficult to find peace and economy",
      "tending to bring together or unite, attending sports events can have a unifying effect on a community",
      "identification with the feelings or thought of another, he feels great deal of empathy for sb's suffering",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 447,
    question: "utopia",
    answer: "a fictional place that where everything is good乌托邦",
    options: [
      "a fictional place that where everything is good乌托邦",
      "加深的 deepening split between",
      "to control/direct by a rule, Diabetics often use insulin to regulate their suger blood",
      "to depict visually or describe in words, she portrayed her boyfriend as tall, even though he was in fact short",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 448,
    question: "veracity",
    answer: "truthfulness, 真实性,The veracity of the story of yong george washington chopping down the cherry tree is questioned by serious historians",
    options: [
      "to occur again, repeatedly, the headache that he got as a child recur when he eats too much ice cream",
      "truthfulness, 真实性,The veracity of the story of yong george washington chopping down the cherry tree is questioned by serious historians",
      "love of mankind, he domonstrated philanthropy by cooking and serving meals to the less fortunate",
      "pertaining to financial matters财政，the account double check the finacial books at the end of fiscal year",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 449,
    question: "viable",
    answer: "capable of living,可行的, the plans for the skyscraper are viable; construction will begin immediately",
    options: [
      "our analysis of the project revealed that it was made of carbon",
      "capable of living,可行的, the plans for the skyscraper are viable; construction will begin immediately",
      "willing to obey someone else, the youngest wolves submissive to the older, stronger more experienced wolves",
      "the beginning of a document or introductory statement, 前言，导言，序言, the preamble to the school board meeting stated that they would disscuss some...",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 450,
    question: "vie",
    answer: "to compete, Sheryl vied with her best friend for a promotion",
    options: [
      "to compete, Sheryl vied with her best friend for a promotion",
      "to compete, Sheryl vied with her best friend for a promotion",
      "本土的",
      "equal in value, equivalent amounts of money",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 451,
    question: "vigilant",
    answer: "警惕的,constantly alert, watchful, wary, the vigilant father guarded at the door to keep the children from seeing the Easter Bunny at work",
    options: [
      "警惕的,constantly alert, watchful, wary, the vigilant father guarded at the door to keep the children from seeing the Easter Bunny at work",
      "碎片, dropped vase shattered into a dozen fragments",
      "规范，被认可的社会标准It is difficult to go against norms of the society",
      "to establish the truth, or validity of, there is little evidence to prove you claim that you were in the shower during the crime",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 452,
    question: "virtually",
    answer: "adv for the most part; almost entirely, 几乎，in 1983, Tom Cruise was virtually known outside his small group of friends",
    options: [
      "adv for the most part; almost entirely, 几乎，in 1983, Tom Cruise was virtually known outside his small group of friends",
      "虚构的her imaginar friend stu is just a figment",
      "挥霍",
      "栖息地，the inhabitant of the ocean depths often look like fictional creatures",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 453,
    question: "visible",
    answer: "able to be seen, on a clear day, mount hood is visible from most locations in portland",
    options: [
      "The shoes I wanted to order from the store are, unfortunately, no longer available",
      "to appease or soothe, the beleaguered general tried to pacify his fierce attacker by sending him a flower",
      "able to be seen, on a clear day, mount hood is visible from most locations in portland",
      "分发，分配，sb distribute sth to someplace",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 454,
    question: "visual",
    answer: "pertaining to seeing, 视觉的，the film had great visual effects, such as fireballs and flying people",
    options: [
      "实例in this instance i disagree",
      "pertaining to seeing, 视觉的，the film had great visual effects, such as fireballs and flying people",
      "The boss will chastise the employees for leaving early",
      "牛",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 455,
    question: "voluntary",
    answer: "having free will，自主性, he made a voluntary decision to confess, hoping that his cooperation would reduce his punishment",
    options: [
      "强调",
      "agreement or congruence和谐we are unable to live together in harmony",
      "荒谬",
      "having free will，自主性, he made a voluntary decision to confess, hoping that his cooperation would reduce his punishment",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 456,
    question: "welfare",
    answer: "well-being, happiness or health, 福利，the country provided free health coverage for the welfare of its citizens",
    options: [
      "pertaining to financial matters财政，the account double check the finacial books at the end of fiscal year",
      "well-being, happiness or health, 福利，the country provided free health coverage for the welfare of its citizens",
      "胰岛素",
      "I am an early raiser and my wife usually sleep late, so we decided to compromise and woke up at 10:00 am",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 457,
    question: "whimsical",
    answer: "异想天开，诙谐的，怪诞的，determined by chance or impulse, the author turned out to be just as whimsical as the playful and amusing character in her book",
    options: [
      "异想天开，诙谐的，怪诞的，determined by chance or impulse, the author turned out to be just as whimsical as the playful and amusing character in her book",
      "仪式，one of the group's religious ritual is to abstain from eating break for a week.",
      "voters turnout is low in this city, most residents are complacent about the current state of politics",
      "细胞",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 458,
    question: "wily",
    answer: "诡计多端的",
    options: [
      "this location is completely secure",
      "How do you deal with adversity in life/work?",
      "love of mankind, he domonstrated philanthropy by cooking and serving meals to the less fortunate",
      "诡计多端的",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 459,
    question: "wither",
    answer: "to shrink, 枯萎, the flower withered and died when the plant was left without water a month",
    options: [
      "变形的deformed face",
      "The house features an additional bedroom that could be used as guest room or an office",
      "a state of permanence, peace, or order, Having lived in four different cities in the past two years, he is now craved stability",
      "to shrink, 枯萎, the flower withered and died when the plant was left without water a month",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 460,
    question: "xenophobia",
    answer: "ZIN uh foh bee uh, a fear of people from other countries, Despite his xenophobia, he packed his bags, got on the plane, and started to explore different countries",
    options: [
      "ZIN uh foh bee uh, a fear of people from other countries, Despite his xenophobia, he packed his bags, got on the plane, and started to explore different countries",
      "Many scientists speculate that exposure to music at a young age is connected the advanced intelligence",
      "to show off, to display ostentatiously炫耀, she likes to flaunt her wealth by wearing expensive jewelry in public",
      "长袍, I would have been a drug queen named foxy codone, if it was not for that white robed god in the sky",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 461,
    question: "yearn",
    answer: "to desire strongly, 向往， he yearned to get back all her favorite baby toys her mom had donated to others",
    options: [
      "to desire strongly, 向往， he yearned to get back all her favorite baby toys her mom had donated to others",
      "尊重 show deference to sb",
      "to be in agreement, to be similar, to communicate by exchange of letters",
      "渴望",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 462,
    question: "yield",
    answer: "to give or supply, The tomato plant will yield a huge number of tomatoes",
    options: [
      "the geologist was hoping to accumulate more rock specimens on his trip out west",
      "to give or supply, The tomato plant will yield a huge number of tomatoes",
      "争吵，the white car stops, the driver jumps out, and a physical brawl ensues.",
      "pertaining to financial matters财政，the account double check the finacial books at the end of fiscal year",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 463,
    question: "yoke",
    answer: "to join together, two oxen were yoked together and hooked up to pull the plow",
    options: [
      "traits or qualities of something, one of the properties of dry ice is that it is very cold",
      "to join together, two oxen were yoked together and hooked up to pull the plow",
      "便携式摄像机, we offer wide range of product from camcorders to flat-screen TVs",
      "The family decided to abbreviate their vacation when a hurricane threatened the island",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 464,
    question: "zenith",
    answer: "the time at which something is most powerful, his career is now at its zenith",
    options: [
      "she was so artistic that even her fruit bowel arranged in a beautiful manner",
      "the whole experience was completely different from what we expected",
      "the time at which something is most powerful, his career is now at its zenith",
      "If you compare the living between paris and New York, renting in paris is much cheaper",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 465,
    question: "smite",
    answer: "strike with a firm blow, he smited the water with his sword; be strongly attracted to someone or sth, you got smitten",
    options: [
      "strike with a firm blow, he smited the water with his sword; be strongly attracted to someone or sth, you got smitten",
      "when the gardener was bit by the snake, the doctor give him an antidote to prevent the posion from taking effect",
      "voters turnout is low in this city, most residents are complacent about the current state of politics",
      "you must assess the effort you have put in to the task",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 466,
    question: "bozo",
    answer: "a stupid or foolish person, you are shithead bozo",
    options: [
      "In certain church services, a benediction is a particular kind of blessing.",
      "Bill Gates has contributes millions of dollars to stop the spread of HIV in Africa",
      "a stupid or foolish person, you are shithead bozo",
      "校内的, the intramural football league had teams made up of inhabitants at each of the university's dorms",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 467,
    question: "womb",
    answer: "子宫，发源地, why does you fight for life stop at a woman's womb?",
    options: [
      "to give or supply, The tomato plant will yield a huge number of tomatoes",
      "the objective of us is to maintain the world peace",
      "a state of permanence, peace, or order, Having lived in four different cities in the past two years, he is now craved stability",
      "子宫，发源地, why does you fight for life stop at a woman's womb?",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 468,
    question: "oppress",
    answer: "压迫, much like the women you are trying to oppress",
    options: [
      "before buying a dog, you need to consider whether or not you'll be able to take care of it",
      "浮躁",
      "The stray dog was captured by dogcatcher",
      "压迫, much like the women you are trying to oppress",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 469,
    question: "rebed",
    answer: "长袍, I would have been a drug queen named foxy codone, if it was not for that white robed god in the sky",
    options: [
      "to appease or soothe, the beleaguered general tried to pacify his fierce attacker by sending him a flower",
      "长袍, I would have been a drug queen named foxy codone, if it was not for that white robed god in the sky",
      "The skaters continuously moved around the rink all night",
      "with their soft fur and large eyes, puppies are appealing to almost everyone",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 470,
    question: "reform",
    answer: "改革，how about fighting against gun reform laws that could prevent school shootings",
    options: [
      "笨拙的",
      "改革，how about fighting against gun reform laws that could prevent school shootings",
      "开脱，to free completely from blame, to exculpate开脱 the jury exonerated the accused",
      "the bilingual teacher could speak to her student both in english and spanish",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 471,
    question: "fetuses",
    answer: "胎儿，speaking of fetuses, we are late for Lil nas x's baby shower",
    options: [
      "胎儿，speaking of fetuses, we are late for Lil nas x's baby shower",
      "接踵而至，接着发生",
      "pertaining to a practical point-of-view,务实,my father is always taking a pragmatic approach, reminding me to be practical instead of impulsive",
      "谚语He remembered the old adage look before you leap",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 472,
    question: "footage",
    answer: "镜头,Danville Costco video Footage shows both men could have walked away, DA",
    options: [
      "尊重 show deference to sb",
      "镜头,Danville Costco video Footage shows both men could have walked away, DA",
      "加快 post office expedite mail delivery",
      "刺穿的",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 473,
    question: "filing",
    answer: "备案，The DA's office said it is not filing charges in the Danvile Costoco beating case due to lack of sufficient evidence",
    options: [
      "Make sure to make attention in class, or you will have trouble with the homework",
      "胰岛素",
      "to come before something, smoke and loud noises preceded the volcanic eruption",
      "备案，The DA's office said it is not filing charges in the Danvile Costoco beating case due to lack of sufficient evidence",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 474,
    question: "surveillance",
    answer: "监控，surveillance footage(监控镜头)shows two men fighting following a likely verbal altercation in the costco parking lot",
    options: [
      "Let's try not to argue over who wash dishes tonight",
      "The judge adjured him to answer truthfully",
      "the bilingual teacher could speak to her student both in english and spanish",
      "监控，surveillance footage(监控镜头)shows two men fighting following a likely verbal altercation in the costco parking lot",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 475,
    question: "prosecution",
    answer: "起诉，there was not enough evidence to bring prosecution on this case",
    options: [
      "the primary reason he took a test prep course was to raise his test scores",
      "The football players consumed so much food, that it was difficult to keep the refrigerator stocked",
      "起诉，there was not enough evidence to bring prosecution on this case",
      "武断的 sb is dogmatic on sth",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 476,
    question: "unprovoked",
    answer: "无缘无故的，无端的，Danville resident who was hospitalized following the fight, told media that the fight was unprovoked",
    options: [
      "very important, the most crucial moments in someplace are...",
      "子宫，发源地, why does you fight for life stop at a woman's womb?",
      "无缘无故的，无端的，Danville resident who was hospitalized following the fight, told media that the fight was unprovoked",
      "Make sure to make attention in class, or you will have trouble with the homework",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 477,
    question: "patch",
    answer: "news reporter, Blackburn told the patch he is now declining to comments on the advice of his attorneys",
    options: [
      "Many beliefs, such as the idea that earth is flat, turn out to be wrong.",
      "capable of living,可行的, the plans for the skyscraper are viable; construction will begin immediately",
      "news reporter, Blackburn told the patch he is now declining to comments on the advice of his attorneys",
      "格言警句 adage, an authoritative saying, no pain, no gain is a dictum",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 478,
    question: "prevailing",
    answer: "胜诉, achieving success in legal proceeding, the likelihood of prevailing in court was pretty low.",
    options: [
      "in a large city, there is so much activity that it is difficult to find peace and economy",
      "不合情理的，extremly wrong or bad, without a moral guide, the actions of crimainal was so unconscionable the not even his lawyer could come up with a good reason to let him go free",
      "穿透，to pass through, enter, or pierce, the doc waited for the needle to penetrate the vein",
      "胜诉, achieving success in legal proceeding, the likelihood of prevailing in court was pretty low.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 479,
    question: "preliminary",
    answer: "初步的, it would not likely get past a preliminary hearing, and a judge could potentially criticize the office for doing sth",
    options: [
      "to anger, to stimulate, to cause, if you see a snake, do not provoke it or it may strike",
      "初步的, it would not likely get past a preliminary hearing, and a judge could potentially criticize the office for doing sth",
      "Many scientists speculate that exposure to music at a young age is connected the advanced intelligence",
      "to become worse or fall apart变坏abandon house begin to deteriorate",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 480,
    question: "incitement",
    answer: "煽动，鼓动，plainly be constructed as incitement to violence",
    options: [
      "栖息地snakes perfer a sunny and dry habitat",
      "煽动，鼓动，plainly be constructed as incitement to violence",
      "to establish the truth, or validity of, there is little evidence to prove you claim that you were in the shower during the crime",
      "very important, the most crucial moments in someplace are...",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 481,
    question: "hurled",
    answer: "投掷，愤慨的说，Blackburn said last week that the man in the Coolla was waiting for his spot, and hurled insults in his direction",
    options: [
      "投掷，愤慨的说，Blackburn said last week that the man in the Coolla was waiting for his spot, and hurled insults in his direction",
      "it is common knowledge that exercise is good for your health",
      "The family decided to abbreviate their vacation when a hurricane threatened the island",
      "半透明的",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 482,
    question: "latch",
    answer: "车门锁,快速走进，The driver of a dark car latches onto a white car",
    options: [
      "车门锁,快速走进，The driver of a dark car latches onto a white car",
      "暂定的，实验，made or done as a trial, experiment, or attempt, unsure, uncertain, these plans are tentative, we may change them at a later time",
      "to join together, two oxen were yoked together and hooked up to pull the plow",
      "检察官",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 483,
    question: "brawl",
    answer: "争吵，the white car stops, the driver jumps out, and a physical brawl ensues.",
    options: [
      "Sleep is central to strong health",
      "I was asleep, but still conscious of the rain beating against the window",
      "children depend on their parents",
      "争吵，the white car stops, the driver jumps out, and a physical brawl ensues.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 484,
    question: "ensue",
    answer: "接踵而至，接着发生",
    options: [
      "接踵而至，接着发生",
      "a fictional place where everything is bad反乌托邦 the hunger games is set in a dydtopia",
      "this location is completely secure",
      "The wealthy benefactor wished to remain anonymous; she didn't want anyone to know her name",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 485,
    question: "mascara",
    answer: "睫毛膏",
    options: [
      "pertaining to seeing, 视觉的，the film had great visual effects, such as fireballs and flying people",
      "In certain church services, a benediction is a particular kind of blessing.",
      "睫毛膏",
      "分发，分配，sb distribute sth to someplace",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 486,
    question: "rodent",
    answer: "啮齿动物",
    options: [
      "啮齿动物",
      "In certain church services, a benediction is a particular kind of blessing.",
      "going beyond what is on the surface, deep,深刻的，深入的，she gave us a profound understanding of human life",
      "He couldn't deal with the adulation of his fans",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 487,
    question: "game",
    answer: "vild mammals or birds hunted for sport or food",
    options: [
      "A venus flytrap is a carnivorous plant that it gains nutrition from the insects it traps.",
      "胜诉, achieving success in legal proceeding, the likelihood of prevailing in court was pretty low.",
      "The boy who broke the lamp wasn't the boy who was punished, it was frustratingly arbitrary",
      "vild mammals or birds hunted for sport or food",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 488,
    question: "jury",
    answer: "陪审团",
    options: [
      "陪审团",
      "excessive昂贵的，the sky-high prices were exorbitant",
      "After Tara learned that her finace had lied to her, she decided to cancel the wedding",
      "说教的intended to teach or educate, aesop's fables is didactic literature",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 489,
    question: "verdict",
    answer: "判决书",
    options: [
      "to spread throughout, the small of my mom's cookies is starting to pervade my room and make my mouth water",
      "判决书",
      "Obey the rules or prepare to suffer the consequences",
      "I was asleep, but still conscious of the rain beating against the window",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 490,
    question: "plumber",
    answer: "管道工",
    options: [
      "Her background in Roman Language was helpful in her trip to Europe",
      "eager to believe,轻信的，易上当的，sb is so credulous",
      "管道工",
      "to come before something, smoke and loud noises preceded the volcanic eruption",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 491,
    question: "notorious",
    answer: "臭名昭著的",
    options: [
      "臭名昭著的",
      "a social blunder, an embarrassing mistake, 失礼, burping after you eat it's considered a gaffe",
      "the fisherman cast its hook into the water, hoping for a bite",
      "the cause of my lateness was that the bus broke down and I had to work 10 blocks.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 492,
    question: "foul",
    answer: "犯规，污秽",
    options: [
      "谚语He remembered the old adage look before you leap",
      "to show off, to display ostentatiously炫耀, she likes to flaunt her wealth by wearing expensive jewelry in public",
      "to reduce or take away the value of有损于 sth will not detract sb's joy/fame",
      "犯规，污秽",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 493,
    question: "ostentatious",
    answer: "炫耀",
    options: [
      "Since Rhonda only answered three of the ten questions, she was certain she had failed the exam",
      "炫耀",
      "The wealthy benefactor wished to remain anonymous; she didn't want anyone to know her name",
      "精明的he is a shrewd person and he is shrewd enough",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 494,
    question: "auspicious",
    answer: "吉祥的",
    options: [
      "short trip短途旅行take a one-day excursion to sp nearby",
      "吉祥的",
      "He amalgamate his company with another",
      "Detectives look for concretes evidence, such as hairs and fingerprint, when solving a crime",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 495,
    question: "exaggeration",
    answer: "夸张",
    options: [
      "夸张",
      "I awoke in the middle night to a loud clamor, my neighbors were arguing again",
      "to control/direct by a rule, Diabetics often use insulin to regulate their suger blood",
      "炫耀",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 496,
    question: "sprinter",
    answer: "短跑运动员",
    options: [
      "Most kids feels pressure to conform to the standards of their peers",
      "Her background in Roman Language was helpful in her trip to Europe",
      "短跑运动员",
      "stephen king is an accomplished writer, with over forty books to his name",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 497,
    question: "clumsy",
    answer: "笨拙的",
    options: [
      "something unusual, significant, or impressive, a solar eclipse is a natural phenomenon that some people will never witness",
      "her ability to play piano is staggering, she can play the hardest pieces effortlessly.",
      "笨拙的",
      "I awoke in the middle night to a loud clamor, my neighbors were arguing again",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 498,
    question: "incompetent",
    answer: "无法胜任的",
    options: [
      "hard to pin down, evasive, 难以琢磨的，困难的the answer to this question was elusive",
      "different, incompatible,不同的 the two cultures were so utterly disparate",
      "the hokey player had several artificial teeth to replace the ones he had lost during the season",
      "无法胜任的",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 499,
    question: "plot",
    answer: "阴谋",
    options: [
      "阴谋",
      "he is a famous architect who designed building so that they would organically fit into their surroundings",
      "the primary reason he took a test prep course was to raise his test scores",
      "when I lost my job, my expensive night on the town ceased",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 500,
    question: "dorm",
    answer: "宿舍",
    options: [
      "截获，侦听 The FBI intercpeted several phone calls that warned of a dangerous plot",
      "we want an outdoor wedding, but we have an alternative locations if it rains",
      "宿舍",
      "夸张",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 501,
    question: "bestow",
    answer: "赐给",
    options: [
      "He couldn't deal with the adulation of his fans",
      "赐给",
      "it is common knowledge that exercise is good for your health",
      "威胁Mrs. Lewis's voice sounded ominous when she told the class it was time for a little test",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 502,
    question: "merit",
    answer: "优点",
    options: [
      "优点",
      "aggregate number of unemployed",
      "to regard with contempt蔑视, sb didained sb for sth",
      "推断I can infer from her tan that she had vacationed in the caribbean",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 503,
    question: "lobbyist",
    answer: "说客",
    options: [
      "Given that you hate crowds, I assumed you wouldn't want my extra tickets for the concert tonight",
      "罪魁祸首，who is culprit?",
      "说客",
      "coming into being,新出现的, an emerging market, cade slowly emerging from his shell",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 504,
    question: "limp",
    answer: "跛行",
    options: [
      "The red tuxedo was conspicuous among the classic black ones",
      "跛行",
      "a fictional place that where everything is good乌托邦",
      "The politician was such a confident person that even when he was behind the polls, he was still convinced he could win",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 505,
    question: "antique",
    answer: "古董",
    options: [
      "含义，意味, when you said I looked healthy, was that really an implication that I have put on weight?",
      "湿透的，she liked how inexpensive she's umbrella was, up untill it's poor quality left her drenched in the rain",
      "贡献the wealthy business man gives a generous offering to the church",
      "古董",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 506,
    question: "dresser",
    answer: "梳妆台",
    options: [
      "梳妆台",
      "The sound of the car alarm downstairs annoyed the residents who were trying to sleep",
      "very small, The baby spider was so minute that one could barely see them",
      "to escape, to avoid逃避，规避，回避 celebrity evade paparazzi on XXX",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 507,
    question: "menacing",
    answer: "险恶的",
    options: [
      "long teeth and ears are characteristic of rabbits",
      "管道工",
      "险恶的",
      "long teeth and ears are characteristic of rabbits",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 508,
    question: "sly",
    answer: "狡猾的she had a sly personality/sly sip of water",
    options: [
      "to cry out with sudden emotion, often in pain or surprise惊呼sb exclaimed at something",
      "to use up花费expend financial resources on sth",
      "打败，the thief had to admit defeat when he found the police had surrouned him",
      "狡猾的she had a sly personality/sly sip of water",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 509,
    question: "shrewd",
    answer: "精明的he is a shrewd person and he is shrewd enough",
    options: [
      "the hound dog has acute sense of smell",
      "精明的he is a shrewd person and he is shrewd enough",
      "穿透，to pass through, enter, or pierce, the doc waited for the needle to penetrate the vein",
      "He amalgamate his company with another",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 510,
    question: "translucent",
    answer: "半透明的",
    options: [
      "there is a strong connection between salary and education level",
      "adv for the most part; almost entirely, 几乎，in 1983, Tom Cruise was virtually known outside his small group of friends",
      "半透明的",
      "父权社会the women linve in the patriarchy wanted to expand the votes to include them",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 511,
    question: "perspicuous",
    answer: "明显的，清晰的",
    options: [
      "Detectives look for concretes evidence, such as hairs and fingerprint, when solving a crime",
      "明显的，清晰的",
      "climatic changes have been reported in the sourthern regions, many of which have been experiencing record high temperatures",
      "In order to better understand history, we need to study context of certain historical event",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 512,
    question: "indigenous",
    answer: "本土的",
    options: [
      "Given that you hate crowds, I assumed you wouldn't want my extra tickets for the concert tonight",
      "to anger, to stimulate, to cause, if you see a snake, do not provoke it or it may strike",
      "分散 police dispersed the crowd.",
      "本土的",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 513,
    question: "peruse",
    answer: "细读",
    options: [
      "厌恶人类者 the misanthrope refused to join the community  for their annual holiday party",
      "细读",
      "辩护人",
      "穿透，to pass through, enter, or pierce, the doc waited for the needle to penetrate the vein",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 514,
    question: "preposterous",
    answer: "荒谬",
    options: [
      "说教的intended to teach or educate, aesop's fables is didactic literature",
      "荒谬",
      "an amount that is taken away from something, A reduction in the number of wolves in YellowStone park led to a resurgence of buffalo in that area",
      "full of doubt, 半信半疑的 Jerry's dubious claim that he could fly like superman",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 515,
    question: "repel",
    answer: "击退,驱除，抵制",
    options: [
      "pertaining to one's sense of right and wrong, the senator made the moral decision not to accept the money from the lobbyist",
      "击退,驱除，抵制",
      "The celebrity was so intimidating, I was not sure how to approach him",
      "罪魁祸首，who is culprit?",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 516,
    question: "credence",
    answer: "信任",
    options: [
      "to look at as a source of information, The handout refers to the lecture's earlier speech",
      "say or read aloud sb dictate sth to sb",
      "信任",
      "to serve as a warning or prediction伏笔,the dark clouds foreshadow a great storm apporaching",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 517,
    question: "convene",
    answer: "召集，召开",
    options: [
      "equal in value, equivalent amounts of money",
      "召集，召开",
      "放大Tiny cells can be viewed through a microscope because it will magnify them to 400 times their actual size",
      "I awoke in the middle night to a loud clamor, my neighbors were arguing again",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 518,
    question: "stringent",
    answer: "严格,demanding",
    options: [
      "尊重 show deference to sb",
      "to rise in opposition to an establish ruler, The teenagers chose to rebel against the unfair dress code by wearing purple sneakers",
      "严格,demanding",
      "he is an adept basketball player",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 519,
    question: "intervene",
    answer: "干预",
    options: [
      "the golden retreiver was amiable, she excitedly greeted every person he saw",
      "a part considered in relation to the whole, 比重，比例，this minor traffic accident is small in proportion to what is going on in thw world",
      "an aggregate flower; an aggregate fruit(strawberry, raspberry, blackberry)",
      "干预",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 520,
    question: "legible",
    answer: "清晰的，易读的",
    options: [
      "the instructor would never concede that he had made a mistake in grading the exam",
      "On Valentine's day, Farhad was feeling amorous, so he took his girlfriend to a romantic dinner",
      "清晰的，易读的",
      "capable of living,可行的, the plans for the skyscraper are viable; construction will begin immediately",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 521,
    question: "fierce",
    answer: "凶猛的",
    options: [
      "凶猛的",
      "skilled in doing something, 精通, she is so proficient at her martial art that she was able to best her sensei",
      "武断的 sb is dogmatic on sth",
      "pertaining to one's sense of right and wrong, the senator made the moral decision not to accept the money from the lobbyist",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 522,
    question: "pierce",
    answer: "刺穿的",
    options: [
      "强调",
      "Most kids feels pressure to conform to the standards of their peers",
      "刺穿的",
      "退化 sth/ sb is degenerated",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 523,
    question: "beleaguered",
    answer: "围困",
    options: [
      "unusual, different from the normal standard古怪，反常的 she is quite an eccentric lady",
      "the act of mentioning something, At lunch, he made a reference to the fact he...",
      "围困",
      "professional philosophers writings often appear abstruse",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 524,
    question: "vein",
    answer: "静脉",
    options: [
      "Obey the rules or prepare to suffer the consequences",
      "静脉",
      "equal in value, equivalent amounts of money",
      "to regard with contempt蔑视, sb didained sb for sth",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 525,
    question: "impulsive",
    answer: "浮躁",
    options: [
      "浮躁",
      "he adhere to muslim faith",
      "the primary reason he took a test prep course was to raise his test scores",
      " My guidance counselor belittled my high school record by telling me that not everybody belongs in colledge.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 526,
    question: "drenched",
    answer: "湿透的，she liked how inexpensive she's umbrella was, up untill it's poor quality left her drenched in the rain",
    options: [
      "湿透的，she liked how inexpensive she's umbrella was, up untill it's poor quality left her drenched in the rain",
      "阻碍missing his front teeth impede his ability to speak clearly",
      "He amalgamate his company with another",
      "the students were ambitious, they wanted to learn everything the school could teach them",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 527,
    question: "camcorder",
    answer: "便携式摄像机, we offer wide range of product from camcorders to flat-screen TVs",
    options: [
      "The wealthy benefactor wished to remain anonymous; she didn't want anyone to know her name",
      "君主制 the british monarchy has sustatined for amlmost a millennium",
      "便携式摄像机, we offer wide range of product from camcorders to flat-screen TVs",
      "When Alex asked her mom if they could go to the museum, she responded, certainly",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 528,
    question: "disbelief",
    answer: "when she told me that I had won the lottery, my first reaction was disbelief.",
    options: [
      "Jes couldn't play sports due to her chronic asthma",
      "when she told me that I had won the lottery, my first reaction was disbelief.",
      "睫毛膏",
      "The popular hotel is in such demand, that it  has limited availability.",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 529,
    question: "dungeons",
    answer: "地牢",
    options: [
      "提议",
      "假说 the science experiment proved the student's hypothesis was false",
      "my purse contain tissue paper, lipstack, and day calender",
      "地牢",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 530,
    question: "resurgence",
    answer: "再起，复兴",
    options: [
      "发白热光的，emitting light as a result of being heated, the meteor become incandescent as it hurled toward the earth",
      "暂时的, he can come back to work when he is feeling better, but in the interim, he should rest",
      "the agreement between republicans and democrats was bipartisan",
      "再起，复兴",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 531,
    question: "insulin",
    answer: "胰岛素",
    options: [
      "Are there any foods that you abhor?",
      "胰岛素",
      "暂定的，实验，made or done as a trial, experiment, or attempt, unsure, uncertain, these plans are tentative, we may change them at a later time",
      "Jes couldn't play sports due to her chronic asthma",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 532,
    question: "diabetics",
    answer: "糖尿病患者",
    options: [
      "州际公路the family drove through an interstate highway from their home in Texas to their new home Florida",
      "糖尿病患者",
      "providing an immediate advantage,应急之际 it is expedient to do something",
      "The historian referred to the annals of 10th century Egyptians to write his paper",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 533,
    question: "abstain",
    answer: "弃权，放弃",
    options: [
      "弃权，放弃",
      "to anger, to stimulate, to cause, if you see a snake, do not provoke it or it may strike",
      "Given that you hate crowds, I assumed you wouldn't want my extra tickets for the concert tonight",
      "谚语He remembered the old adage look before you leap",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 534,
    question: "crave",
    answer: "渴望",
    options: [
      "to offer or hold out to someone for acceptance, 提供，提出，because your proffer of repayment for the movie tickets was too little, I will not buy them to you",
      "渴望",
      "Given my finiancial circumstances, I am not sure I should be going on vacation this summer",
      "to represent, to portray,描绘 dipicted sth as ...",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 535,
    question: "famine",
    answer: "饥荒",
    options: [
      "打败，the thief had to admit defeat when he found the police had surrouned him",
      "饥荒",
      "Are there any foods that you abhor?",
      "when I lost my job, my expensive night on the town ceased",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 536,
    question: "devise",
    answer: "发明",
    options: [
      "say or read aloud sb dictate sth to sb",
      "full of doubt, 半信半疑的 Jerry's dubious claim that he could fly like superman",
      "A venus flytrap is a carnivorous plant that it gains nutrition from the insects it traps.",
      "发明",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 537,
    question: "crooked",
    answer: "歪，弯曲",
    options: [
      "existing perpetually without change",
      "love of mankind, he domonstrated philanthropy by cooking and serving meals to the less fortunate",
      "歪，弯曲",
      "to give or supply, The tomato plant will yield a huge number of tomatoes",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 538,
    question: "mosoon",
    answer: "梅雨",
    options: [
      "假说 the science experiment proved the student's hypothesis was false",
      "prior to Copernicus, conventional wisdoms states that the earth is the center of universe.",
      "梅雨",
      "ZIN uh foh bee uh, a fear of people from other countries, Despite his xenophobia, he packed his bags, got on the plane, and started to explore different countries",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 539,
    question: "rouse",
    answer: "唤醒",
    options: [
      "唤醒",
      "very important, the most crucial moments in someplace are...",
      "The patient heart stopped, the doctor said it was due to cardiac arrest",
      "to maintain or keep alive, in order to preserve fresh bread, make sure to keep it in dark, air-tight place",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 540,
    question: "procecutor",
    answer: "检察官",
    options: [
      "长袍, I would have been a drug queen named foxy codone, if it was not for that white robed god in the sky",
      "诡计多端的",
      "检察官",
      "唤醒",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 541,
    question: "defender",
    answer: "辩护人",
    options: [
      "being the most important force or component统治，主宰,dominant leader/color",
      "梳妆台",
      "辩护人",
      "The children chanted as they sang ring around the rosie",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 542,
    question: "defeat",
    answer: "打败，the thief had to admit defeat when he found the police had surrouned him",
    options: [
      "打败，the thief had to admit defeat when he found the police had surrouned him",
      "警惕的,constantly alert, watchful, wary, the vigilant father guarded at the door to keep the children from seeing the Easter Bunny at work",
      "Her apartment consists of three rooms: a bedroom, a bathroom, and a kitchen",
      "武断的 sb is dogmatic on sth",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 543,
    question: "snap",
    answer: "折断，the tension on the rope was so tight that he was afraid it would snap at any time",
    options: [
      "The skaters continuously moved around the rink all night",
      "to show off, to display ostentatiously炫耀, she likes to flaunt her wealth by wearing expensive jewelry in public",
      "折断，the tension on the rope was so tight that he was afraid it would snap at any time",
      "子宫，发源地, why does you fight for life stop at a woman's womb?",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 544,
    question: "cellular",
    answer: "细胞",
    options: [
      "She makes an adequate amount of money, but she still could not afford to go on a fancy vacation",
      "Currently, builders are eagerly to construct houses in neighborhoods with growing populations",
      "牛",
      "细胞",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 545,
    question: "adamant",
    answer: "坚定的",
    options: [
      "My contribution to the bake sale was three dozen oatmeal-raised cookies",
      "The patient heart stopped, the doctor said it was due to cardiac arrest",
      "说客",
      "坚定的",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 546,
    question: "impulse",
    answer: "冲动",
    options: [
      "The wealthy benefactor wished to remain anonymous; she didn't want anyone to know her name",
      "to become worse or fall apart变坏abandon house begin to deteriorate",
      "栖息地，the inhabitant of the ocean depths often look like fictional creatures",
      "冲动",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 547,
    question: "oxen",
    answer: "牛",
    options: [
      "In contemporary society, cell phones and laptops are very normal",
      "identification with the feelings or thought of another, he feels great deal of empathy for sb's suffering",
      "this location is completely secure",
      "牛",
    ]
  },
];
